[["sabella levan million in vermillion ph @isabellalevan @amillioninvermillion @isabellalevan music production : million in vermillion amillioninvermillion album : https://isabellalevanmusicbandcamp.com", [[1, 5, "PERSON"]]], ["Fp tip Staff maxu mad 72ip Name : abel sandman 16th , xxiol date of employment : april post : driver lyl d", [[34, 38, "PERSON"], [39, 46, "PERSON"]]], ["sinclair rachel sinclair abel sandman peport Captain hermann !", [[25, 29, "PERSON"], [30, 37, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"], [53, 60, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"], [9, 15, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"]]], ["physical description fits but chel abel abel sandman 26th , xx17 date of death : ` estimated time : 11308 cause of death : car rec= to allow face is too from the fourth finger up sinclairi sinclair ander sandman report november accident ' facial charred phalanx : description : proximal Sinclair rachel sinclair alexander report sinclair alexander xx Of", [[35, 39, "PERSON"], [45, 52, "PERSON"], [312, 321, "PERSON"], [179, 187, "PERSON"], [179, 187, "PERSON"], [296, 302, "PERSON"], [179, 187, "PERSON"], [179, 187, "PERSON"]]], ["only thing i 've found on them is an article reflting the snapdragon 's ' defamatory statements \" still act ; in the the he of lower = on the for her of romy the om for gross ; in ljail jaw threw labelling the group anarchists \" and claiming everything in the pamphlets is baseless lies . lented", [[197, 201, "PERSON"]]], ["also mentioned he knew my parents ' driver , abel sandman . they", [[45, 49, "PERSON"], [50, 57, "PERSON"]]], ["abel", [[0, 4, "PERSON"]]], ["'m going to untie you now , do n't scream : Abel sandman . why", [[44, 48, "PERSON"], [49, 56, "PERSON"]]], ["the real reason i lost it was because Sake sake was in my parents ' car , with my parents ' driver . Abel", [[101, 105, "PERSON"], [38, 42, "PERSON"]]], ["annabelle she was the most exceptional woman i have ever known . '", [[3, 7, "PERSON"]]], ["leigh x98 annabelle = march I 've spent so much time wondering why them ?", [[13, 17, "PERSON"], [22, 27, "PERSON"]]], ["annabelle . she", [[3, 7, "PERSON"]]], ["' leigh annabelle = march She", [[11, 15, "PERSON"], [20, 25, "PERSON"]]], ["parents left with sandman in the morning aewa november 26th , xxi terrible car accident carrues the sinclairs and their dri !", [[18, 25, "PERSON"], [100, 108, "PERSON"], [100, 108, "PERSON"], [100, 108, "PERSON"], [100, 108, "PERSON"]]], ["did n't think someone wolld ever sing it to me again : @lck L tiv e I 've missed it Sandman : sake : And robin delaney reperye dy colld this have any link to the pamphlets ?", [[84, 91, "PERSON"], [105, 110, "PERSON"], [111, 118, "PERSON"], [94, 98, "PERSON"]]], ["'s like he never existed and then how did sandman manage to fake his death ?", [[42, 49, "PERSON"]]], ["you think it was sandman 's fallt ?", [[17, 24, "PERSON"]]], ["maybe Sake was there in the very beginning maybe he 'd know something And sandman too , since he 's apparently still alive 0 suk ' clock news late fagf dety ictus Mailp oooh what the heck !", [[74, 81, "PERSON"], [6, 10, "PERSON"]]], ["were both part of the phantom scythe : sandman was his getaway driver the day of the explosion . everyone", [[39, 46, "PERSON"], [22, 29, "PERSON"], [30, 36, "PERSON"]]], ["believed sandman died in the car accident with my parents But sake was saying otherwise . What", [[9, 16, "PERSON"], [62, 66, "PERSON"]]], ["sandman november 26th , xxi7 date of time : 130", [[0, 7, "PERSON"]]], ["you 'd better not forget about anslow 's picture . Sandman", [[51, 58, "PERSON"], [31, 37, "PERSON"]]], ["only to be killed for it hundreds of people were killed for it i almost was too Mhk and dylan Sandman za It", [[94, 101, "PERSON"], [88, 93, "PERSON"]]], ["was it was a lie No sandman knew him His body missing . There", [[20, 27, "PERSON"]]], ["more week to go before sandman reaches out to me . Of", [[23, 30, "PERSON"]]], ["sandman . Seeing", [[0, 7, "PERSON"]]], ["was involved in the allendale bombing and sandman was their getaway driver . i", [[42, 49, "PERSON"], [20, 30, "LOC"]]], ["are a strange man , sandman . you", [[20, 27, "PERSON"]]], ["remember when i told you my parents died in a car accident with their driver , sandman ?", [[79, 86, "PERSON"]]], ["truth about sandmans past involvement and his present actions . And", [[12, 19, "PERSON"]]], ["who my parents really were Chckle So according to sandman and what you overheard from the king 's right hand . it", [[50, 57, "PERSON"]]], ["from sandman , nor my parents . Or", [[5, 12, "PERSON"]]], ["he decided to kill off sandman said he thought they wanted t leave . It", [[23, 30, "PERSON"]]], ["is another thing Sandman found the name of the black haired woman from the carmine camelia . She", [[17, 24, "PERSON"], [71, 90, "LOC"]]], ["october november december xx17 xx17 xx17 xx17 january xx Alexander", [[57, 66, "PERSON"]]], ["those stepping out of the line , or traitors , eradicated no . rachel and alexander , your parents , they knew the leader . You", [[74, 83, "PERSON"], [115, 121, "PERSON"], [63, 69, "PERSON"]]], ["hyacinth Episode eint knl lshal yqhr parents swpl Sinclair accicent ate adal alexans alexander 26 t novembet 1130 ate@t death ; of de car sigeatrdbrge 87caen pusel etipitio raice They knew whq the leader was n wp } 4 ' la 1 ] iragedy 1 thans nore \" 76 & { da xaksaa november 26th , 16y november z6th , xxt car car sinclairs and sinclairs and yqh know what that means , right ?", [[85, 94, "PERSON"], [50, 58, "PERSON"], [50, 58, "PERSON"], [197, 203, "PERSON"], [50, 58, "PERSON"], [50, 58, "PERSON"]]], ["loved rachel and alexander , but it was them or . well", [[17, 26, "PERSON"], [6, 12, "PERSON"]]], ["Whether they wanted to quit or not They were guilty Rachel adwell alexander sinclair james sinclair x982 xxiz xx980 xxiz And", [[66, 75, "PERSON"], [76, 84, "PERSON"], [76, 84, "PERSON"], [52, 58, "PERSON"], [76, 84, "PERSON"], [76, 84, "PERSON"]]], ["'s never let anything slip though X as reminiscing about rachel and alexander ?", [[68, 77, "PERSON"], [57, 63, "PERSON"]]], ["' N ' Splashl woosh= Officer sinclair ?", [[29, 37, "PERSON"], [29, 37, "PERSON"], [29, 37, "PERSON"], [29, 37, "PERSON"]]], ["blue 0e Thanks . sinclair", [[17, 25, "PERSON"], [17, 25, "PERSON"], [17, 25, "PERSON"], [17, 25, "PERSON"]]], ["here . Sinclair", [[7, 15, "PERSON"], [7, 15, "PERSON"], [7, 15, "PERSON"], [7, 15, "PERSON"]]], ["Bomb disposal unit reporting the threat has been successfully neutralized Officer sinclair !", [[82, 90, "PERSON"], [82, 90, "PERSON"], [82, 90, "PERSON"], [82, 90, "PERSON"]]], ["sinclair", [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"]]], ["tristan sinclair head of ardhalis police department Uncle ?", [[8, 16, "PERSON"], [8, 16, "PERSON"], [8, 16, "PERSON"], [0, 7, "PERSON"], [8, 16, "PERSON"]]], ["fantastic , welcome to the teami nice to meet you , officer My name is kieran white Lauren sinclair . it", [[91, 99, "PERSON"], [71, 77, "PERSON"], [78, 83, "PERSON"], [84, 90, "PERSON"], [91, 99, "PERSON"], [91, 99, "PERSON"], [91, 99, "PERSON"]]], ["sinclair is right . i", [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"]]], ["ca n't stop now but the worst part of it all good morning , officer sinclair !", [[68, 76, "PERSON"], [68, 76, "PERSON"], [68, 76, "PERSON"], [68, 76, "PERSON"]]], ["officer sinclair here an emergency ?", [[8, 16, "PERSON"], [8, 16, "PERSON"], [8, 16, "PERSON"], [8, 16, "PERSON"]]], [", you said you 're a sinclair so", [[21, 29, "PERSON"], [21, 29, "PERSON"], [21, 29, "PERSON"], [21, 29, "PERSON"]]], ["since tristan sinclair is the chief of police . you", [[14, 22, "PERSON"], [14, 22, "PERSON"], [14, 22, "PERSON"], [6, 13, "PERSON"], [14, 22, "PERSON"]]], ["sinclair !", [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"]]], ["{ @al Sht Officer sinclair and i will pursue !", [[18, 26, "PERSON"], [18, 26, "PERSON"], [18, 26, "PERSON"], [18, 26, "PERSON"]]], ["will be provided for you in the interrogation room : William hawkes , lauren sinclair , impressive team work . You", [[77, 85, "PERSON"], [61, 67, "PERSON"], [70, 76, "PERSON"], [77, 85, "PERSON"], [56, 60, "PERSON"], [77, 85, "PERSON"], [61, 67, "PERSON"], [61, 67, "PERSON"], [77, 85, "PERSON"], [53, 60, "PERSON"], [61, 67, "PERSON"]]], ["lauren sinclair patrol unit nthprecinct ardhalis police department Hey", [[7, 15, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"], [7, 15, "PERSON"], [7, 15, "PERSON"], [7, 15, "PERSON"]]], ["officer sinclair !", [[8, 16, "PERSON"], [8, 16, "PERSON"], [8, 16, "PERSON"], [8, 16, "PERSON"]]], ["'ve known you for a long time , kieran : and i can assure you that \" naivety \" really does n't look good on you Crack Detective sinclair is back in the field . Tuk", [[128, 136, "PERSON"], [32, 38, "PERSON"], [128, 136, "PERSON"], [128, 136, "PERSON"], [128, 136, "PERSON"]]], ["so , i hate to break it to you but there 's snitches everywhere in the police i know there must be you said as much on the night we met i 'm sure all your fellow police officers despise the leader , But harvey Officer sinclairi he was so sweet , so considerate and genuine all the time . god", [[218, 226, "PERSON"], [203, 209, "PERSON"], [218, 226, "PERSON"], [190, 196, "PERSON"], [218, 226, "PERSON"], [218, 226, "PERSON"]]], ["Officer sinclair here : pxvxvsh ?", [[8, 16, "PERSON"], [8, 16, "PERSON"], [8, 16, "PERSON"], [8, 16, "PERSON"]]], ["'re one breath away from rioting in the streets chief sinclair managed to stop a revolt last time , but the shock is much more serious now this assassin snuck inside the tower the most highly guarded section of the prison like it was a a vulgar shop !", [[54, 62, "PERSON"], [54, 62, "PERSON"], [54, 62, "PERSON"], [54, 62, "PERSON"]]], ["heard me sinclair is n't here which makes you two bit more tolerable dost mine ears deceive me ?", [[9, 17, "PERSON"], [9, 17, "PERSON"], [9, 17, "PERSON"], [9, 17, "PERSON"]]], ["'s learned from her mistakes no 5s I do n't want officer sinclair involved with anything phantom scythe related . last", [[57, 65, "PERSON"], [57, 65, "PERSON"], [89, 96, "PERSON"], [97, 103, "PERSON"], [57, 65, "PERSON"], [57, 65, "PERSON"]]], ["to say this matter is to remain strictly confidential between the four of us sinclair will not be part of this operation . Lieutenant", [[77, 85, "PERSON"], [77, 85, "PERSON"], [77, 85, "PERSON"], [77, 85, "PERSON"]]], ["we both know he 's jealous that tristan sinclair got made chief of police . no", [[40, 48, "PERSON"], [40, 48, "PERSON"], [40, 48, "PERSON"], [32, 39, "PERSON"], [40, 48, "PERSON"]]], ["we meet again , detective sinclair . or", [[26, 34, "PERSON"], [26, 34, "PERSON"], [26, 34, "PERSON"], [26, 34, "PERSON"]]], ["sinclair will assist you . Yes", [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"]]], ["the hell are you doing , sinclair ?", [[25, 33, "PERSON"], [25, 33, "PERSON"], [25, 33, "PERSON"], [25, 33, "PERSON"]]], ["you completely lost it sinclair ?", [[23, 31, "PERSON"], [23, 31, "PERSON"], [23, 31, "PERSON"], [23, 31, "PERSON"]]], [", we meet again , detective sinclair . Or", [[28, 36, "PERSON"], [28, 36, "PERSON"], [28, 36, "PERSON"], [28, 36, "PERSON"]]], ["that all you 've got , detective sinclair ?", [[33, 41, "PERSON"], [33, 41, "PERSON"], [33, 41, "PERSON"], [33, 41, "PERSON"]]], ["tell you just because i like you , sinclair . The", [[35, 43, "PERSON"], [35, 43, "PERSON"], [35, 43, "PERSON"], [35, 43, "PERSON"]]], ["sinclair is back . Officer", [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"]]], ["sinclair finally report the assassin escaped i and two other officers were in pursuit but they were soon outpaced i pursued him for as long as i could and engaged him in a fight before losing him as well However , officer sinclair got close enough to him to be able to tell that we are dealing with a man , tall , slim and in his twenties thirties . i", [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"]]], ["' m pleasantly surprised sinclair or What happened in here ?", [[25, 33, "PERSON"], [25, 33, "PERSON"], [25, 33, "PERSON"], [25, 33, "PERSON"]]], ["then the killer escaped through the window which is when i spotted him : Good analysis , sinclair : hmph . leave", [[89, 97, "PERSON"], [89, 97, "PERSON"], [89, 97, "PERSON"], [89, 97, "PERSON"]]], ["the investigating to the detectives , officer sinclair . An", [[46, 54, "PERSON"], [46, 54, "PERSON"], [46, 54, "PERSON"], [46, 54, "PERSON"]]], ["Officer sinclair shk The assassin you encountered tonight is none other than : The purple hy acinth Purple hyacinth prologue ost available on all free streaming services . music", [[8, 16, "PERSON"], [8, 16, "PERSON"], [8, 16, "PERSON"], [8, 16, "PERSON"]]], ["and mrs . sinclair . n", [[10, 18, "PERSON"], [10, 18, "PERSON"], [10, 18, "PERSON"], [10, 18, "PERSON"]]], ["knew and i did n't even suspect it until i saw anslow 's picture : ke jout November 26th , xx17 terrible car accident carries the sinclairs and their driver i was a fool ten years ago and nothing has changed the car was borrowed from a random rich family . that", [[130, 138, "PERSON"], [47, 53, "PERSON"], [130, 138, "PERSON"], [130, 138, "PERSON"], [130, 138, "PERSON"]]], ["lauren sinclairi Lalren , meet the newest addition to our precinct . Kieran", [[7, 15, "PERSON"], [69, 75, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"], [7, 15, "PERSON"], [7, 15, "PERSON"], [7, 15, "PERSON"]]], ["lauren sinclairi Lalren , meet the newest addition to our precinct . His", [[7, 15, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"], [7, 15, "PERSON"], [7, 15, "PERSON"], [7, 15, "PERSON"]]], ["'m lauren : The pleasure is mine , officer sinclair . I", [[43, 51, "PERSON"], [3, 9, "PERSON"], [43, 51, "PERSON"], [43, 51, "PERSON"], [43, 51, "PERSON"]]], ["called her sinclair I see this might indeed become problematic you know i 'm almost jealous it 's always the purple hyacinth who gets the fancy jobs if apostle vi !", [[11, 19, "PERSON"], [11, 19, "PERSON"], [11, 19, "PERSON"], [11, 19, "PERSON"]]], ["thought you were a threat Hmm : right \" a threat curious i thought the same when i saw those shurikens flying at me : Well , i did n't expect the law abiding office sinclair to turn into a mastermind criminal . Birds", [[165, 173, "PERSON"], [165, 173, "PERSON"], [165, 173, "PERSON"], [165, 173, "PERSON"]]], ["8 5 mtar Pn p kys9ie ] ika aa hue aewa november 26th , xx17 terrible car accident carrues the sinclairs and their drive What is your angle , lauren ?", [[94, 102, "PERSON"], [141, 147, "PERSON"], [94, 102, "PERSON"], [94, 102, "PERSON"], [94, 102, "PERSON"]]], [", good morning , officer sinclair !", [[25, 33, "PERSON"], [25, 33, "PERSON"], [25, 33, "PERSON"], [25, 33, "PERSON"]]], ["sinclair ?", [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"]]], ["lalren sinclair . got", [[7, 15, "PERSON"], [7, 15, "PERSON"], [7, 15, "PERSON"], [7, 15, "PERSON"]]], ["no one has ever gotten close enough to be able to describe him as precisely as officer sinclair did tonight . We", [[87, 95, "PERSON"], [87, 95, "PERSON"], [87, 95, "PERSON"], [87, 95, "PERSON"]]], ["may have lost valuable assets tonight but now we know who we 're looking for , at least the details you were able to provide tonight are of immeasurable value as always well done , officer sinclair \" well done ?", [[189, 197, "PERSON"], [189, 197, "PERSON"], [189, 197, "PERSON"], [189, 197, "PERSON"]]], ["this is n't his usual political terrorism rocca and grayson were recently recruited as double agents they were assigned to try to infiltrate the phantom scythe 's underground network only those with the highest security clearance were aware seems like the leader is always one step ahead of us hawkes , ladell sinclair i want to thank you three for coming so quickly tonight the investigation unit will take care of the rest you are now dismissed Yes siri What a prick . good", [[310, 318, "PERSON"], [303, 309, "PERSON"], [294, 300, "PERSON"], [303, 309, "PERSON"], [310, 318, "PERSON"], [256, 262, "PERSON"], [145, 152, "PERSON"], [153, 159, "PERSON"], [310, 318, "PERSON"], [294, 300, "PERSON"], [42, 47, "PERSON"], [52, 59, "PERSON"], [294, 300, "PERSON"], [310, 318, "PERSON"], [294, 300, "PERSON"]]], ["the sinclair 's daughter is a waste of time . she", [[4, 12, "PERSON"], [4, 12, "PERSON"], [4, 12, "PERSON"], [4, 12, "PERSON"]]], ["sinclair was still in the investigation unit , 4j she might already have a lead by now . well", [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"]]], ["then i heard the sinclairs daughter was an officer at the precinct that arrested anslow . I", [[17, 25, "PERSON"], [81, 87, "PERSON"], [17, 25, "PERSON"], [17, 25, "PERSON"], [17, 25, "PERSON"]]], [", officer 25 sinclair !", [[13, 21, "PERSON"], [13, 21, "PERSON"], [13, 21, "PERSON"], [13, 21, "PERSON"]]], ["are dealing with the purple hyacinth again : Thanks to officer sinclair , we now know he is male , arolnd 5\"9 tall , and 20 to 30 years old . He", [[63, 71, "PERSON"], [63, 71, "PERSON"], [63, 71, "PERSON"], [63, 71, "PERSON"]]], ["came up with few theories that might be useful to the investiga officer sinclair by the looks of the bags under your eyes have no doubt you spent the entire night obsessing over this and concocted many theories as always your attention to details and analytical perception on crime scene is remarkable however cufu must remind you . any", [[72, 80, "PERSON"], [72, 80, "PERSON"], [72, 80, "PERSON"], [72, 80, "PERSON"]]], ["sinclair . Lauren", [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [11, 17, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"]]], ["drop like flies around you , sinclair . There", [[29, 37, "PERSON"], [29, 37, "PERSON"], [29, 37, "PERSON"], [29, 37, "PERSON"]]], [", only until we get the evidence . sinclair", [[35, 43, "PERSON"], [35, 43, "PERSON"], [35, 43, "PERSON"], [35, 43, "PERSON"]]], ["and will inform chief sinclair to keep an eye on you as well Fup Transcript chow s cn detective lauren sincla witness tim sake 70 Sake : but i 'm not !", [[22, 30, "PERSON"], [76, 80, "PERSON"], [96, 102, "PERSON"], [22, 30, "PERSON"], [22, 30, "PERSON"], [122, 126, "PERSON"], [22, 30, "PERSON"]]], ["sinclair", [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"]]], ["since the allendale train station tragedy nobody could 've known they would strike there what horrible senseless massacre sinclair : what did you say ?", [[122, 130, "PERSON"], [122, 130, "PERSON"], [122, 130, "PERSON"], [122, 130, "PERSON"], [10, 20, "LOC"], [10, 33, "LOC"]]], ["40 eafe sake j88 \" ever since the allendale train station tragedy nobody could 've known would strike there what horrible senseless masaaer sinclair : what did you say ?", [[140, 148, "PERSON"], [140, 148, "PERSON"], [140, 148, "PERSON"], [8, 12, "PERSON"], [140, 148, "PERSON"], [34, 44, "LOC"], [34, 57, "LOC"]]], ["10 I m det Officer sinclair . i", [[19, 27, "PERSON"], [19, 27, "PERSON"], [19, 27, "PERSON"], [19, 27, "PERSON"]]], ["are other cases that could be linked to this one what the hell is this , sinclair ?", [[73, 81, "PERSON"], [73, 81, "PERSON"], [73, 81, "PERSON"], [73, 81, "PERSON"]]], ["have my althorization to proceed with the appeal Detective march and detective cooper will be in charge of the case . sinclair", [[118, 126, "PERSON"], [79, 85, "PERSON"], [118, 126, "PERSON"], [59, 64, "PERSON"], [118, 126, "PERSON"], [118, 126, "PERSON"]]], ["'ve done all the work , sinclair , and it 's impressive : pkt Cooper and i will not let it go to waste . You", [[24, 32, "PERSON"], [62, 68, "PERSON"], [24, 32, "PERSON"], [24, 32, "PERSON"], [24, 32, "PERSON"]]], ["endless vicious cycle : Carefll , sinclair . you", [[34, 42, "PERSON"], [34, 42, "PERSON"], [34, 42, "PERSON"], [34, 42, "PERSON"]]], ["i 'll continle to always do my best for them So what about you , sinclair ?", [[65, 73, "PERSON"], [65, 73, "PERSON"], [65, 73, "PERSON"], [65, 73, "PERSON"]]], ["ms . sinclair has grown into a fine lady oh", [[5, 13, "PERSON"], [5, 13, "PERSON"], [5, 13, "PERSON"], [5, 13, "PERSON"]]], ["ms sinclair looks ravishing tonighti Hawkes !", [[3, 11, "PERSON"], [37, 43, "PERSON"], [3, 11, "PERSON"], [3, 11, "PERSON"], [37, 43, "PERSON"], [37, 43, "PERSON"], [3, 11, "PERSON"], [37, 43, "PERSON"]]], ["we should n't have argued in front of the sinclair 's picture : They were always exemplary people There was never an argument we colldn't settle . Or", [[42, 50, "PERSON"], [42, 50, "PERSON"], [42, 50, "PERSON"], [42, 50, "PERSON"]]], ["have n't indeed i assume you 're ms . sinclair ?", [[38, 46, "PERSON"], [38, 46, "PERSON"], [38, 46, "PERSON"], [38, 46, "PERSON"]]], ["hyacinth Episode Good evening It 's been a long time , william : and nice to finally meet you , ms sinclair you look just as lovely as they describe you . Thank", [[99, 107, "PERSON"], [99, 107, "PERSON"], [58, 62, "PERSON"], [99, 107, "PERSON"], [99, 107, "PERSON"], [55, 62, "PERSON"]]], ["was excited to learn you 've been invited to the sinclair 's party . i", [[49, 57, "PERSON"], [49, 57, "PERSON"], [49, 57, "PERSON"], [49, 57, "PERSON"]]], ["'s going on by the way , your place looks splendid ms sinclair would you mind showing 4s around ?", [[54, 62, "PERSON"], [54, 62, "PERSON"], [54, 62, "PERSON"], [54, 62, "PERSON"]]], ["my god , ms . sinclair , you look so pale !", [[14, 22, "PERSON"], [14, 22, "PERSON"], [14, 22, "PERSON"], [14, 22, "PERSON"]]], ["what about sinclair ?", [[11, 19, "PERSON"], [11, 19, "PERSON"], [11, 19, "PERSON"], [11, 19, "PERSON"]]], ["sinclair was home the entire night . dozens", [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "PERSON"]]], ["of glests , chief sinclair and lord rhysmel can confirm it . I", [[18, 26, "PERSON"], [36, 43, "PERSON"], [18, 26, "PERSON"], [18, 26, "PERSON"], [18, 26, "PERSON"]]], ["good news for you , sinclair !", [[20, 28, "PERSON"], [20, 28, "PERSON"], [20, 28, "PERSON"], [20, 28, "PERSON"]]], ["would send chills down anyone 's spine : but i 'm glad officer sinclair is no longer suspected I also have good newsconcerning chow 's case . The", [[63, 71, "PERSON"], [127, 131, "PERSON"], [63, 71, "PERSON"], [63, 71, "PERSON"], [63, 71, "PERSON"]]], ["officer sinclair here An emergency ?", [[8, 16, "PERSON"], [8, 16, "PERSON"], [8, 16, "PERSON"], [8, 16, "PERSON"]]], ["no problem , officer sinclair . it", [[21, 29, "PERSON"], [21, 29, "PERSON"], [21, 29, "PERSON"], [21, 29, "PERSON"]]], ["Ffrwn 01 , sinclair , lieltenant hawkes is briefing 4s on the itinerary change . what", [[11, 19, "PERSON"], [33, 39, "PERSON"], [11, 19, "PERSON"], [11, 19, "PERSON"], [33, 39, "PERSON"], [33, 39, "PERSON"], [11, 19, "PERSON"], [33, 39, "PERSON"]]], [", detective sinclair . i", [[12, 20, "PERSON"], [12, 20, "PERSON"], [12, 20, "PERSON"], [12, 20, "PERSON"]]], ["'s two to zero sinclair . did", [[15, 23, "PERSON"], [15, 23, "PERSON"], [15, 23, "PERSON"], [15, 23, "PERSON"]]], ["i 'm ready to bet we 're looking at the effects of olden viper venom : forensic examiner andrew lawes forensic unit 1th precinct ardhalis police department the venom spreads rapidly through the bloodstream and burns through all types of tissues with Skin and cartilage , while also causing mass hemorrhaging < it", [[89, 95, "PERSON"], [96, 101, "PERSON"]]], ["hermann requested we look more closely into this list cuack Lila , andrew , grace , lukas , lalren . Feels", [[67, 73, "PERSON"], [76, 81, "PERSON"], [0, 7, "PERSON"], [60, 64, "PERSON"], [84, 89, "PERSON"]]], ["enough dobce they 've been organized under an anonymous leader for the past decade though at first it was just him and the thirteen \" apostles \" They 're the ones who claimed responsibility for allendale train station . T", [[134, 142, "PERSON"], [56, 62, "PERSON"], [194, 204, "LOC"], [194, 217, "LOC"]]], ["days we 're down to seven apostles . only", [[26, 34, "PERSON"]]], [", let 's assume the apostles are the closest to the leader . Our", [[20, 28, "PERSON"], [52, 58, "PERSON"]]], ["Yep , except that the apostles ' identities are also unknown . Seriously", [[22, 30, "PERSON"]]], ["apostles are far more traceable than the leader , though . Each", [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [41, 47, "PERSON"]]], ["holds all the pieces of the puzzle except the apostles and the leader himself . I", [[46, 54, "PERSON"], [63, 69, "PERSON"]]], ["lied about the apostles identity !", [[15, 23, "PERSON"]]], ["if that 's what 's necessary Stbz The apostles never show themselvesi it 's always an anonymous messenger who gives us our directives . they", [[38, 46, "PERSON"], [96, 105, "PERSON"]]], ["izth xxis 13 for mhe kliin ' orld by monarchy the phantom = opposition to the wi consolidate ' e inibend clear mcosuse | ihej can oveathrow eovoz m the dark until the & g ; it relies on , ' the crovn and the class consid : ine class udy 243 |eaths , irain 328 and 176 wle hus real dung the wond \" r and that the more and of to { be was ' 8 to in the of agent , now isth would try to heported that tbe the of the the castle 0n group e train on the sectin ; the on the 13th , c af me was led to and 7 m apostles the apostles are the leaded 5 closest accomplices . le", [[501, 509, "PERSON"], [50, 57, "PERSON"]]], ["were only a handful of members back then , closer to the apostles . Apparently", [[57, 65, "PERSON"]]], ["the very few others became his first apostles . Sad", [[37, 45, "PERSON"]]], ["were apostles . Let", [[5, 13, "PERSON"]]], ["xxi7 : ferrible accident e terrible carries accident carries the ' thei the ' thei They Were yen hllne qe valllelceller tsrataly aaitiotate| Apostles ; I d knup Oinnd Yv v | ves Your parenis nere tro of the leader s first aposies : Bhbur it ca nt be they could nt have They knew who the leader was wm h how ?", [[141, 149, "PERSON"], [207, 213, "PERSON"]]], ["in the phantom scythe Only the apostles know the leader . (", [[31, 39, "PERSON"], [49, 55, "PERSON"], [7, 14, "PERSON"], [15, 21, "PERSON"]]], ["they were apostles and what ?", [[10, 18, "PERSON"]]], ["cevnu vvz Tw Cmg Apostles . 78u", [[17, 25, "PERSON"]]], ["'ve never believed in that stuff they were apostles . But", [[43, 51, "PERSON"]]], ["lieutenant is up for the challenge everyonei 8 ( leerse ' worte sahd D d tatdur mamsters satbrida vorie they were apostles . No", [[114, 122, "PERSON"]]], ["he know they were apostles ?", [[18, 26, "PERSON"]]], ["snapdragon 's work dismissed as an anarchist pack of lies by all the official newspapers we were only a handful of members back then , closer to the apostles . tap", [[149, 157, "PERSON"]]], ["the very few others became his first apostles . They", [[37, 45, "PERSON"]]], ["the phantom scythe the apostles ' speciality is to find any of your weaknesses and use them against you . stl", [[23, 31, "PERSON"], [4, 11, "PERSON"], [12, 18, "PERSON"]]], ["this is serious official business after all apostles are required to wear one when they speak to their subordinates Li do n't be ridicllous . Haha", [[44, 52, "PERSON"]]], ["they were apostles . his", [[10, 18, "PERSON"]]], ["the parallel poles , the mighty huntress who never misses her target mv mvnvlh artemisi and morpheus the magician whose tricks will make you wonder if you re dreaming !", [[79, 86, "PERSON"], [92, 100, "PERSON"], [93, 100, "PERSON"]]], ["among you would like to test their hlnting skills against the unmatched lady artemis ?", [[77, 84, "PERSON"]]], [", artemis zephyr . those", [[2, 9, "PERSON"], [10, 16, "PERSON"]]], ["high king 0f ardhalis philip aevasther The high queen of ardhalis lizbeth aevasther Your majesty !", [[29, 38, "PERSON"], [29, 38, "PERSON"], [66, 73, "PERSON"], [29, 38, "PERSON"], [22, 28, "PERSON"], [29, 38, "PERSON"]]], ["once again the noble emblem of our ancient family the aevasther 's hyacinths , graceful flowers but poisonous for anyone who tries to bruise them , has been tainted by the blood of his victims the leader is sending us a message , but we shall not let ourselves be intimidated we will not show fear in front of these criminals . Measures", [[54, 63, "PERSON"], [54, 63, "PERSON"], [79, 84, "PERSON"], [197, 203, "PERSON"], [54, 63, "PERSON"], [54, 63, "PERSON"]]], ["phantom scythe has always targeted the citadel 's ruling family . Aevasther", [[66, 75, "PERSON"], [66, 75, "PERSON"], [0, 7, "PERSON"], [8, 14, "PERSON"], [66, 75, "PERSON"], [66, 75, "PERSON"]]], ["fardhalis aevasther apphalis # yacinta covus , venusd ) sicut A threat , more likely . What", [[10, 19, "PERSON"], [10, 19, "PERSON"], [10, 19, "PERSON"], [10, 19, "PERSON"]]], ["since the aevasthers ordered the assassination of those poor people . hsy", [[10, 19, "PERSON"], [10, 19, "PERSON"], [10, 19, "PERSON"], [10, 19, "PERSON"]]], ["since the aevasthers ordered the assassination of those poor people htbsy They signed their own demise . mk", [[10, 19, "PERSON"], [10, 19, "PERSON"], [10, 19, "PERSON"], [10, 19, "PERSON"]]], ["ca n't believe athena asked one of them to go on stage . Alright", [[15, 21, "PERSON"]]], ["for the others i 've cooperated with mctrevor , ryan flemmings and a woman called beatrice blakesley . Hm", [[82, 90, "PERSON"], [91, 100, "PERSON"], [37, 45, "PERSON"], [21, 27, "PERSON"], [48, 52, "PERSON"], [53, 62, "PERSON"]]], ["'ve been investigating beatrice blakesley . We", [[23, 31, "PERSON"], [32, 41, "PERSON"]]], ["I 've heard that beatrice blakesley will be put to trial tomorrow . Her", [[17, 25, "PERSON"], [26, 35, "PERSON"]]], ["music and art page ) donate on patreon for blood and murder : patreon com / sophism editor : hb klein Assistants : @neekaarts @zaphyrae @akikakies @yersiniaapestiss music by sophism singer : beatrice @slavica krzelj Ephemerys co creator sophism co creator toilet paper Y'all wonder who stole all the toilet papers thow We stole all of them just for you 1 5 you Are n't we so thoughtful ca nt reach it", [[191, 199, "PERSON"]]], ["'ve got a lot of stuff to cover regarding what blakesley revealed tonight . he", [[47, 56, "PERSON"]]], [", mctrevor and blakesley were all arrested ?", [[15, 24, "PERSON"], [2, 10, "PERSON"]]], [", mctrevor , blakesley and colden . They", [[13, 22, "PERSON"], [2, 10, "PERSON"], [27, 33, "PERSON"]]], ["blakesley colden . and", [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [10, 16, "PERSON"]]], ["being imported into the City in antipication overdue revolution , hclrevor , anslow;| blakesley & nd colden were managing the front business iook care of papertrails , cleaned the money , red the real transacti apostle vi !", [[86, 95, "PERSON"], [77, 83, "PERSON"], [101, 107, "PERSON"]]], ["First mctrevor , anslow , blakesley and colden e= killed by the purple hy acinth almieih tkotelo hotel iiutic | ice cesttnga Four", [[26, 35, "PERSON"], [6, 14, "PERSON"], [17, 23, "PERSON"], [40, 46, "PERSON"]]], ["uk Lgeek uilk cukk ccuack Belladonna davenport messenger vi !", [[26, 36, "PERSON"], [37, 46, "PERSON"], [47, 56, "PERSON"]]], ["'s heri mm Kujn Hestiai Belladonna davenport Let 's make it spicy : rreaders \" tears co creator co creator / artist", [[24, 34, "PERSON"], [35, 44, "PERSON"]]], ["hyacinth Episode Belladonna davenport Did you know ?", [[17, 27, "PERSON"], [28, 37, "PERSON"]]], ["i chose blades over guns for very different reasons , belladonna . Will", [[54, 64, "PERSON"]]], ["the night we infiltrated the restalrant i overheard him telling belladonna about it . I", [[64, 74, "PERSON"]]], ["clack cla ( Belladona davenport well , this is about to get Interesting . Lonely", [[22, 31, "PERSON"]]], ["should know , davenport things were actually going pretty well before i left . And", [[14, 23, "PERSON"]]], ["'s no hiding anything from you , belladona davenport . What", [[43, 52, "PERSON"]]], ["name 's davenport you could call her an \" old friend \" of mine ,", [[8, 17, "PERSON"]]], [", quite a lot in fact Turns out flemmings had a rendez vous with davenport the assassin i just told you about she is involved in the apostle 's operation as a sort of supervisor they 'll have a meeting at the carmen camelia in a few days with the apostle 's messenger turns out the apostle xi !", [[65, 74, "PERSON"], [258, 267, "PERSON"], [32, 41, "PERSON"]]], ["took over the leader 's operation for his own interest , whatever they are however , the leader is aware of his little rebellion thanks to davenport 's intel . i", [[139, 148, "PERSON"], [14, 20, "PERSON"]]], ["the leader has ordered |he to keep eye on his gimmicks and to elid te the rebels when the right time comes , belladonnf davenport ps assassin m0 co co long ons , \" 1 role in the weapon opdration : superviser , ng i d of nuisances ; double aqen r an flemmings role in the weapon operation : overseas associate , |ensuring the weapons deliver to ardhalis , altering and erasin traces of il7 transaction gett ; egal Circus tickets i rrivate reception ?", [[120, 129, "PERSON"], [4, 10, "PERSON"], [249, 258, "PERSON"]]], ["up , davenport . let", [[5, 14, "PERSON"]]], [", davenport that 's the name of the assassin who killed harvey !", [[2, 11, "PERSON"], [56, 62, "PERSON"]]], ["evening blanca , jane . Hahaha", [[8, 14, "PERSON"], [17, 21, "PERSON"]]], ["take care of it , blanca . i'l", [[18, 24, "PERSON"]]], ["i used to have a sister too . daena", [[30, 35, "PERSON"]]], ["i ca nt since you seem to find the situation so funn ladell you ll be in charge of this case and an related paperwork at your orders my not nearly as handsome lieutenant what happened to your butler my lady ?", [[53, 59, "PERSON"], [53, 59, "PERSON"], [192, 198, "PERSON"]]], ["Ladell , do n't you always have that pocket watch with you ?", [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["That 's kym for you . ladell", [[22, 28, "PERSON"], [22, 28, "PERSON"]]], ["ladell , the patrol is in your charge !", [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["ca n't believe they called us in on our day off sergeant kym ladell patrol unit ilth precinct ardhalis police department and for a simple homicide !", [[61, 67, "PERSON"], [61, 67, "PERSON"]]], ["do n't think it 's a good idea lieutenant hawkes will sergeant ladelli ' would you be so kind as to explain why your desk is becoming a cafe ?", [[63, 69, "PERSON"], [42, 48, "PERSON"], [63, 69, "PERSON"], [42, 48, "PERSON"], [42, 48, "PERSON"], [42, 48, "PERSON"]]], ["llslt M i never thought of you as an early bird , ladell . thmp", [[50, 56, "PERSON"], [50, 56, "PERSON"]]], ["are dead meat , ladell . you", [[16, 22, "PERSON"], [16, 22, "PERSON"]]], ["officer lieutenant hawkes went after her . ladell", [[43, 49, "PERSON"], [19, 25, "PERSON"], [43, 49, "PERSON"], [19, 25, "PERSON"], [19, 25, "PERSON"], [19, 25, "PERSON"]]], ["talk to hawkes and ladell when they get back . Purple", [[19, 25, "PERSON"], [8, 14, "PERSON"], [19, 25, "PERSON"], [8, 14, "PERSON"], [8, 14, "PERSON"], [8, 14, "PERSON"]]], ["hyacinth Episode Lieutenant hawkes , sergeant ladell come in , march and i need to speak with you captain hermann detective march how can we help you ?", [[46, 52, "PERSON"], [106, 113, "PERSON"], [28, 34, "PERSON"], [46, 52, "PERSON"], [63, 68, "PERSON"], [28, 34, "PERSON"], [28, 34, "PERSON"], [28, 34, "PERSON"]]], ["agree with sergeant ladell . It", [[20, 26, "PERSON"], [20, 26, "PERSON"]]], ["hawkes sergeant ladell Will you help us end lune once and for all ?", [[16, 22, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"], [16, 22, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["ladell ?", [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["just slammed a door into me , ladelli ' who the hell stands in a doorway ?", [[30, 36, "PERSON"], [30, 36, "PERSON"]]], ["ladell , at your service , miss . The", [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["stage is yours , sergeant ladell !", [[26, 32, "PERSON"], [26, 32, "PERSON"]]], ["round of applause for our eagle eyed local hero sergeant ladell !", [[57, 63, "PERSON"], [57, 63, "PERSON"]]], ["golden clover is on the right . Ladell", [[32, 38, "PERSON"], [32, 38, "PERSON"], [0, 13, "LOC"]]], [", i am sergeant ladell And", [[16, 22, "PERSON"], [16, 22, "PERSON"]]], ["hawkes , 11th precinct sergeant ladell , 11th precinct please forgive 4s our impromptu visit we 're here on behalf of the investigation unit we just want to quickly follow up on mr anslow 's arrest three weeks ago . ah", [[32, 38, "PERSON"], [181, 187, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"], [32, 38, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["about you , sergeant ladell ?", [[21, 27, "PERSON"], [21, 27, "PERSON"]]], ["ca nt human cont act ladell , when you 're done swooning over the new recruit i need you to h hvf", [[21, 27, "PERSON"], [21, 27, "PERSON"]]], ["white , could you please grab sergeant ladell 's molntain of reports . before", [[39, 45, "PERSON"], [0, 5, "PERSON"], [39, 45, "PERSON"]]], ["lalren , i 'm glad to know you still have eyes alright , ladellc enough , you have work to do and they do n't deserve this shv do n't worry , i'l make sure nobody at the precinct learns about this from us If that 's what you 'd prefer . Oh", [[57, 63, "PERSON"], [57, 63, "PERSON"]]], ["; zklde Lieutenant hawkes , sergeant ladell @au ' A", [[37, 43, "PERSON"], [19, 25, "PERSON"], [37, 43, "PERSON"], [19, 25, "PERSON"], [19, 25, "PERSON"], [19, 25, "PERSON"]]], ["Aaa what a strange day the reports you sent headquarters were full of mistakes and unrepresentative of the quality the 11th precinct is trying to uphold . ladell", [[155, 161, "PERSON"], [155, 161, "PERSON"]]], ["ladell , patrol unit !", [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["'s fortunate we happen to live nearby or maybe it was intentional : two murders back to back make sure we see him but still ca n't catch him : a power play plausible ladell he has been taunting the royal family for years now grisp He co opts their family crest as some sort of sick joke . 4", [[166, 172, "PERSON"], [166, 172, "PERSON"]]], ["ladell That woman drives me insane !", [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["Ladell", [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"]]], [", screw sergeant ladell Present . you", [[17, 23, "PERSON"], [17, 23, "PERSON"]]], ["you please put this pile of paperwork on ladell 's desk when she comes back ?", [[41, 47, "PERSON"], [41, 47, "PERSON"]]], ["sergeant ladell don think we can no not you , march !", [[9, 15, "PERSON"], [9, 15, "PERSON"], [46, 51, "PERSON"]]], ["from you , ladell , yes Stop sulking in your corner and come dance with us N no !", [[11, 17, "PERSON"], [11, 17, "PERSON"]]], ["wowowow owowow ladell ?", [[15, 21, "PERSON"], [15, 21, "PERSON"]]], ["last thing i want to thank everyone who signed up for the security team at viscount redcliff 's ball on the 17th i have forwarded the list to lord rhysmel lieutenant hawkes and sergeant ladell will hold a session for all vollnteers soon to discuss preparation and coordination with other precincts that is all for today dismissed . Dakan", [[186, 192, "PERSON"], [332, 337, "PERSON"], [147, 154, "PERSON"], [166, 172, "PERSON"], [186, 192, "PERSON"], [166, 172, "PERSON"], [166, 172, "PERSON"], [75, 83, "PERSON"], [84, 92, "PERSON"], [166, 172, "PERSON"]]], ["a good day Ladell", [[11, 17, "PERSON"], [11, 17, "PERSON"]]], ["Ladell , are you smok auulug ] nic", [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["is sergeant ladell Message was not received , i repeat message was not received Please repeat what is your location ?", [[12, 18, "PERSON"], [12, 18, "PERSON"]]], ["ladell and lieutenant hawkes please report ct . Again", [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [22, 28, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"], [22, 28, "PERSON"], [22, 28, "PERSON"], [22, 28, "PERSON"]]], ["glass factory located on 73 sherbrooke street where is sergeant ladell ?", [[64, 70, "PERSON"], [64, 70, "PERSON"]]], ["Ladell", [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["king 's right hand dakan rhysmel @uiuk", [[19, 24, "PERSON"], [25, 32, "PERSON"]]], ["dakan", [[0, 5, "PERSON"]]], ["'s dakan . Oh", [[3, 8, "PERSON"]]], [", dakan , it 's been so long !", [[2, 7, "PERSON"]]], ["the way , dakan called last night !", [[10, 15, "PERSON"]]], ["still have n't found anything we need to keep looking K # tk : I have so many things to tell you , ren Tp Qn Sqfbs Your majesty Dakan you", [[128, 133, "PERSON"]]], ["that a threat dakan ?", [[14, 19, "PERSON"]]], [". Dakan", [[2, 7, "PERSON"]]], ["70 Dakani you made it !", [[3, 8, "PERSON"]]], ["on , we all know dakan is really here to see you , uncle . let", [[17, 22, "PERSON"]]], ["sound like an old man , dakan . haha", [[24, 29, "PERSON"]]], ["and dakan were the closest to my parents . f", [[4, 9, "PERSON"]]], ["'re a good man , dakan . i", [[17, 22, "PERSON"]]], ["yet here we are , talking about ending the phantom scythe while its bloodiest assassin stands among us enjoying the show this morning the king 's right hand , sir rhysmel , came to speak with me to establish a plan of action : steps will be taken , and we will release our plans to the public as soon as possible !", [[163, 170, "PERSON"], [43, 50, "PERSON"], [51, 57, "PERSON"]]], ["queeni Sir rhysmel !", [[11, 18, "PERSON"]]], ["have been much better under your reign : you 've gained the sympathy of the people : they 'll fight for you against these monsters . Rhysmel", [[133, 140, "PERSON"]]], ["rhysmel'8 office I know what you re up to . You", [[0, 7, "PERSON"]]], ["his majesty 's right hand , lord rhysmel , has personally requested our public presence at the event . many", [[33, 40, "PERSON"]]], ["know you never meant to kill me . Dylan", [[34, 39, "PERSON"]]], ["' Dylan !", [[2, 7, "PERSON"]]], ["dylan !", [[0, 5, "PERSON"]]], ["come here these are called freesias they symbolize trust purity hey dylan : . hm", [[68, 73, "PERSON"]]], ["Dylani", [[0, 5, "PERSON"]]], ["dad told me it makes men charming that 's why your dad is still single , dylan !", [[73, 78, "PERSON"]]], ["you tie it off there uhum udo glhd Cks Sgrecmh = Vgh dylan , are you okay ?", [[53, 58, "PERSON"]]], ["w Gile Wmp Dylan ?", [[11, 16, "PERSON"]]], ["it was too late . dylan", [[18, 23, "PERSON"]]], ["i wrong abolt yolrs too , dylan ?", [[26, 31, "PERSON"]]], ["flo wer is dylan really dead?2 ?", [[11, 16, "PERSON"]]], ["dylan fotoesh vketr wujt \" Look", [[0, 5, "PERSON"]]], ["the odds that dylan was among them are I know , kym ; i know . You", [[14, 19, "PERSON"]]], ["if i ca n't prove anything i need to at least know what really happened To my parents and to dylan . i", [[93, 98, "PERSON"]]], ["dylan . Thanks", [[0, 5, "PERSON"]]], ["Dylan", [[0, 5, "PERSON"]]], ["Dylan . If", [[0, 5, "PERSON"]]], ["it trle we 'll get to see king edward mr rosenthal ?", [[41, 50, "PERSON"], [31, 37, "PERSON"], [41, 50, "PERSON"]]], ["you , mr . rosenthal !", [[11, 20, "PERSON"], [11, 20, "PERSON"]]], ["rosenthal Dyl we e The", [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [0, 9, "PERSON"]]], ["rosenthal xxo5 xx That", [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [0, 9, "PERSON"]]], ["city was inaugurating a new railway , financed by the late king edward . He", [[64, 70, "PERSON"]]], ["when the royal family is most vulnerable : the death of king edward was the perfect chance to overthrow the whole system : it 's about time the leader made a move !", [[61, 67, "PERSON"], [144, 150, "PERSON"]]], ["' daly november ] 4th , xxi7 the king is dead ' 13th , 10.30.a date that will forever ardhalis ' engaved the when & prince philip by the perpetrated nherits the crown ' the the eves ofcountless of= edward and our \" felbows was present at tne for the this mauguration of which he had nety they november xxi7 . remaui", [[198, 204, "PERSON"], [123, 129, "PERSON"]]], ["edward allendale ' tran statjon moring raltway financed Majesty was members of thecompanied by nobilty : government & nd the the expksion , at the epicenter of ' had no survival dikan rhyhe allendale kings right hand rrain station is he 2 wh many standing they chance aevasty lizbeth queen lauren ollowing \" the next train will leave at 16.45 \" the years to come will be the ibrightest ardhalis has ever known ; ' Gf 1s a harvey officer 18 trista sinclhir chief # uce oliver petective march spi ?", [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [422, 428, "PERSON"], [290, 296, "PERSON"], [276, 283, "PERSON"], [468, 474, "PERSON"], [485, 490, "PERSON"], [7, 17, "LOC"]]], ["were n't even legal under king edward 's rule how did my parents even get them ?", [[31, 37, "PERSON"]]], ["I had told them : i told king edward his policies needed t change . the", [[30, 36, "PERSON"]]], ["lay people lost their jobs for much less were interrogated some had to serve time in jail and some disappeared edward was intransigent and cruel . You", [[111, 117, "PERSON"]]], ["name is elvira llyod , 45 years old , living in the 11th district . pretty", [[8, 14, "PERSON"]]], ["'s had several jobs as manager and is currently the director of the glass factory on sherbrooke street , in the 11th as well Elvira lloyd . huh", [[125, 131, "PERSON"], [132, 137, "PERSON"]]], ["by the way we received the delivery yesterday our last two players are still sticking to the plan like obedient pawns think neither flemmings nor elvira will surprise 4s . tss", [[146, 152, "PERSON"], [132, 141, "PERSON"]]], ["Pit brt pk Pat lloyd inc . glass factory since x Wc ueys lld t glass f sfactorv Did you manage to get hand on the building 's plans ?", [[15, 20, "PERSON"]]], ["will never abandon your feet , my graceful lady !", [[34, 39, "PERSON"]]], ["you know even though you 're such a human disgrace , i 've still dedicated my life to protecting ungrateful cowards like you . it", [[45, 50, "PERSON"]]], ["signs are pretty vious he has no offensive or defensive wounds besides the cut on his neck forensic examiner grace riverhood forensic unit 11th precinct ardhalis police department considering the rotting skin around the cut , the blade must 've been coated powerfll poison : the autopsy will confirm it but", [[109, 114, "PERSON"], [115, 124, "PERSON"]]], ["are circus roy alei Here 's a taste of our upcoming showi The famed killer of the glorious nemean lion a beast whose hide could not be pierced by any human weapon it'sthe man , the myth , the legend heraklesi Floating in the sky twisting and bending the breeze to his will our graceful aerialist zephyri hbrlage bows Accompanied by our lovely blindfolded pianist apolloi Mluml mumcl On", [[277, 282, "PERSON"], [199, 207, "PERSON"], [296, 302, "PERSON"]]], ["We are left trembling with indignation at these disgraceful injustices . Wait", [[51, 56, "PERSON"]]], ["may be tristan 's niece , but she 's a disgrace to the department and sullies your reputation by association : She 's been making amends for her mistake and everyone i do n't care what your precinct thinks of her . glik", [[42, 47, "PERSON"], [7, 14, "PERSON"]]], ["of the original thirteen thuidq Among the people potentially involved , i ve identified gregory mctrevor who 's been previously accused of illegal arms trading . i", [[88, 95, "PERSON"], [96, 104, "PERSON"]]], ["file on gregory mctrevor Is n't that the merchant the investigation unit keeps trying to pin down ?", [[8, 15, "PERSON"], [16, 24, "PERSON"]]], ["this folder , you will find everything you need 1o send gregory mctrevor nis final incarceration . In", [[56, 63, "PERSON"], [64, 72, "PERSON"]]], ["this folder , you will find everything you need \" Good day , officers this folder , you will find everything you need to send gregory mctrevor to his final incarceration . to", [[126, 133, "PERSON"], [134, 142, "PERSON"]]], ["send gregory mctrevor to his final incarceration :", [[5, 12, "PERSON"], [13, 21, "PERSON"]]], ["inside this folder ; 66 you will find everything you need to send gregory mctrevor to his final incarceration ?", [[66, 73, "PERSON"], [74, 82, "PERSON"]]], ["whole operation could be compromised : ' \" and you lose your only chance to stop gregory mctrevor . Apparently", [[81, 88, "PERSON"], [89, 97, "PERSON"]]], ["the seal of secrecy until r leaked outside , the whole e to stop gregory mctrevor lune X vi Good job on the patrol today !", [[65, 72, "PERSON"], [73, 81, "PERSON"]]], ["'s not the most subtle man ever . mctrevor", [[34, 42, "PERSON"]]], ["if it 's the only solution : We 'll find a different way to neutralize mctrevor . I", [[71, 79, "PERSON"]]], ["have the day to verify everything here is in accordance with what is already known of Mr mctrevor ?", [[89, 97, "PERSON"]]], ["the writer holds his own theatrics in very high esteem hilarious and pretentious from what i 've seen in the file , this is the work of a professional it has to be someone with precise knowledge of our investigations on mctrevor pffsh covqb Is it signed ?", [[220, 228, "PERSON"]]], [", i 've been working mctrevor 's case for five years . everyone", [[21, 29, "PERSON"]]], ["your team : stops this exceptional incident shall remain strictly confidential until the case is solved until mctrevor is either behind bars or back home in his bed ' and Am i clear ?", [[110, 118, "PERSON"]]], ["thought you had better manners , mr . mctrevor . That", [[38, 46, "PERSON"]]], ["and their stupid rules . Mctrevori", [[25, 33, "PERSON"]]], ["already told you everything i know I 'm sure you 've gone through a lot of interrogations , mctrevor but you never had one with me slam !", [[92, 100, "PERSON"]]], ["can lie all you want , mctrevor , but we 're going to find this kid , and then . well", [[23, 31, "PERSON"]]], ["mctrevor", [[0, 8, "PERSON"]]], ["did mctrevor say ?", [[4, 12, "PERSON"]]], ["that information top secret until the trial We 'll deal with the official announcement then : what 'll happen to mctrevor in the meantime ?", [[113, 121, "PERSON"]]], ["mctrevor will certainly be incarcerated in the meantime . Whoever", [[0, 8, "PERSON"]]], ["need to act quickly before the other buffoons hear about mctrevor and realize they 're next the detectives still do n't suspect you ?", [[57, 65, "PERSON"]]], [", with all the evidence you gathered and the papers from mctrevor , i think we have everything we need on harry anslow . i", [[57, 65, "PERSON"], [106, 111, "PERSON"], [112, 118, "PERSON"]]], ["Ttor ha including the ones from mctrevor 's fake company The front for the weapons operation : So", [[32, 40, "PERSON"]]], ["were okay with tying mctrevor up , why 's it different when it 's not in his house ?", [[21, 29, "PERSON"]]], ["much , unfortunately he 's not as stupid as mctrevor he knows better than to hide traces of the operation in his office let 's hurry then : we wo n't have a lot of time before the police get here thvd Hold on officer . Are", [[44, 52, "PERSON"]]], ["'re the ones that got mctrevor !", [[22, 30, "PERSON"]]], ["Mctrevor", [[0, 8, "PERSON"]]], ["case is almost as easy as mctrevor 's . the", [[26, 34, "PERSON"]]], ["'s the same logo as the one on mctrevor 's files kazun ' transaction concluded . report", [[31, 39, "PERSON"]]], ["of them had this logo dc which we also found on mctrevor 's stuff . and", [[48, 56, "PERSON"]]], ["blew up a train station full of civilians just to kill one man : who knows what he 'd do to ruin any progress we were making with mctrevor and the others . The", [[130, 138, "PERSON"]]], ["directing a weapons import operation for the leader and that mctrevor was involved of Mctrevor led us to anslow who had that photograph , but nothing else useful . then", [[61, 69, "PERSON"], [105, 111, "PERSON"], [45, 51, "PERSON"]]], ["then there 's everything else we found the company seal on mctrevor and flemmings 's papers report teton transachon aeoncluded The stains on flemmings 's clothes . Whatever", [[59, 67, "PERSON"], [72, 81, "PERSON"]]], ["four morons who got arrested are out of the picture now we have the next steps perfectly under control our project was almost exposed to the police nothing exclldes that they could establish a common denominator between mctrevor and the others . the", [[220, 228, "PERSON"]]], ["'s the same logo as on mctrevor 's papers . #", [[23, 31, "PERSON"]]], ["people take care of the papertrail , i clean the money Give me the names of the people you 're working with and their responsibilities . Harry", [[137, 142, "PERSON"]]], ["hyacinth Episode Apdi please stand asidei Were looking for harry anslowi If you have information come forwardi else , step aside !", [[59, 64, "PERSON"], [65, 71, "PERSON"]]], ["harry anslow knows something y a he had that photograph for a reason . i", [[0, 5, "PERSON"], [6, 12, "PERSON"]]], ["perfect Harry anslow . thtpp", [[8, 13, "PERSON"], [14, 20, "PERSON"]]], ["or harry i ca n't remember . Oh", [[3, 8, "PERSON"]]], ["took it from harry anslow the night of his arrest , did n't you ?", [[13, 18, "PERSON"], [19, 25, "PERSON"]]], ["the phantom scythe is suicide : so i want take down as many people as i can with me . Harry", [[86, 91, "PERSON"], [4, 11, "PERSON"], [12, 18, "PERSON"]]], ["anslow and ryan flemmings !", [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [11, 15, "PERSON"], [16, 25, "PERSON"]]], ["'ve been following anslow the past few days . He", [[19, 25, "PERSON"]]], ["we 'll send them to the wrong address Il leave second letter there with the actual instructions on where to arrest anslow . their", [[115, 121, "PERSON"]]], ["you find anything at anslow 's ?", [[21, 27, "PERSON"]]], ["a small locked storage room and set everything up for anslow there we wo n't be disturbed there . at", [[54, 60, "PERSON"]]], ["on , let 's dance : pvl cuk ' Any sign of anslow ?", [[42, 48, "PERSON"]]], ["lure anslow there so you can knock him out without being seen : Get yourself a cabernet sauvignon first . he'l", [[5, 11, "PERSON"]]], ["still have n't heard from kieran : nor have i dared to go back to the cave not slrprising , considering we were so close to getting calght becalse of me . Anslow", [[155, 161, "PERSON"], [26, 32, "PERSON"]]], ["heard my voice and saw part of my face : It 's a miracle that he did n't remember it . anslow", [[87, 93, "PERSON"]]], ["need to find a way to get to anslow . i", [[29, 35, "PERSON"]]], ["all , we made a pact to not kill each other and lucky for you , i am a man of my word so officer what the hell did you see in anslow 's notebook ?", [[126, 132, "PERSON"]]], ["do n't need to worry about anslow . He", [[27, 33, "PERSON"]]], ["anslow", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["anslow", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["will finally be able to see anslow tomorrow x dembrr of 4;20 22nd date eduled visit I wo n't leave until i get my answers . f@", [[28, 34, "PERSON"]]], ["of lune 's convicts . anslow", [[22, 28, "PERSON"]]], ["are n't mad because i killed these people : You 're mad because i killed anslow . What", [[73, 79, "PERSON"]]], ["is about you and what you found in anslow 's belongings . you", [[35, 41, "PERSON"]]], ["You are n't mad because i killed these people : you 're mad because i killed anslow The selfish hypocrite ?", [[77, 83, "PERSON"]]], ["went gpip too far : pryz You are n't mad because i killed these people : You 're mad becaluse i killed anslow this is not all about anslowi Even if he survived i selfish hypocrite Hw+", [[103, 109, "PERSON"]]], ["about it anslow was in the bar for while before he woke up in the storage room : Lune needed to trick him or at least knock him out . to", [[9, 15, "PERSON"]]], ["is a list of potential lune suspects i struck off the names of the officers and detectives involved in the golden clover raid the night of anslow 's arrest and everyone else whose alibi has already been verified nothing guarantees lune is from our precinct . but", [[139, 145, "PERSON"], [107, 120, "LOC"]]], ["'s around when we captured anslow ah yes !", [[27, 33, "PERSON"]]], ["date she never told me abolt tup It was a relief kieran said she was at l'arlequin the night of anslow 's arrest we officially crossed her off the list but if it 's really as i suspect , what will william do ?", [[96, 102, "PERSON"], [49, 55, "PERSON"], [200, 204, "PERSON"], [197, 204, "PERSON"], [72, 82, "LOC"]]], ["your friends check on it , they 'll see we were both there when anslow was arrested . hmm", [[64, 70, "PERSON"]]], ["i ' 1 p joce ika nar anslow 's picture ?", [[21, 27, "PERSON"]]], ["wanted dirt on sake , who has never been beloved by his colleagues , as you probably noticed . anslow", [[95, 101, "PERSON"], [15, 19, "PERSON"]]], ["showed up in the middle of a police raid to anslow in cuffs and the picture gone . but", [[44, 50, "PERSON"]]], ["you do n't want this picture leaked to yolr superiors , get me anslow 's photo and any copies of it . i", [[63, 69, "PERSON"]]], ["you revealed all of this to me in exchange for anslow 's picture ?", [[47, 53, "PERSON"]]], ["i killed these people : You 're mad because i killed anslow . what", [[53, 59, "PERSON"]]], ["we calght anslow at the golden clover . hmm", [[10, 16, "PERSON"], [24, 37, "LOC"]]], [", i 'll be going now , officer harvey . got", [[31, 37, "PERSON"]]], ["harvey wood patrol unit i1th precinct", [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [7, 11, "PERSON"], [7, 11, "PERSON"]]], ["ardhalis police department You re right harvey !", [[40, 46, "PERSON"]]], ["harvey do n't tell me you also got dragged into her shenanigans thp", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["we 've lost them wait where 's officer harvey ?", [[39, 45, "PERSON"]]], ["n't stay up too late , harvey Purple hyacinth This episode contains images of graphic violence which may be disturbing to some readers . discretion", [[23, 29, "PERSON"]]], ["hey , harvey you 're still there ?", [[6, 12, "PERSON"]]], ["would anyone want to do this to harvey ?", [[32, 38, "PERSON"]]], ["just assumed harvey went home I doubt harvey could have had any personal enemies who would bother to go to such expensive extremes to get rid of him : I 'd guess it 's the phantom scythe taunting us . avbf", [[13, 19, "PERSON"], [172, 179, "PERSON"], [180, 186, "PERSON"]]], [", that 's quite unushal and expensive , whatever the message the killer wanted to send : I wish i could find the assassin who did this to harvey and send him to rot in jail . i", [[138, 144, "PERSON"]]], ["I could 've been the one to kill harvey , you know that ?", [[33, 39, "PERSON"]]], [": i see . Harvey", [[10, 16, "PERSON"]]], [": harvey wood date of birth : april 17th , xxo1 . function", [[2, 8, "PERSON"], [9, 13, "PERSON"], [9, 13, "PERSON"]]], ["still . Harvey", [[8, 14, "PERSON"]]], ["'s not your usual uniform : It 's harvey 's funeral today . Purple", [[34, 40, "PERSON"]]], ["Pf : Oh , harvey my dearest grandson : Why . ?", [[10, 16, "PERSON"]]], ["harvey", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["yet we are standing here mourning the death of a traitor We trusted harvey 5 ' Poor lalren , she seems really upset by his death . We", [[68, 74, "PERSON"]]], ["All my years of research lead nowhere because of this guy name : harvey wood date of birth : april 17th , xxo1 function : spy , 11th precinct , apd in service since : march 23rd , xx26 number of reports : 34 . execution day : december 2oth , xx Spies like him make sure the police ca n't touch the jay nalr phantom scythe : ae y8 , * 45 casu unsolvedd unsolved case All those dropped cases and suspected criminals r let free no wonder 19th , xx26 police arrest suspect tim sake They let criminals walk the streets freely . But", [[65, 71, "PERSON"], [72, 76, "PERSON"], [307, 314, "PERSON"], [315, 321, "PERSON"], [72, 76, "PERSON"], [167, 172, "PERSON"], [473, 477, "PERSON"]]], ["are leaving for the reception at harvey 's house : Are you coming ?", [[33, 39, "PERSON"]]], ["huh i did n't know you were close to harvey . i", [[37, 43, "PERSON"]]], ["'m harvey 's replacement the new mole . I", [[3, 9, "PERSON"]]], ["has suspected connections to your precinct harvey had to be replaced and i was available . it", [[43, 49, "PERSON"]]], ["i think we all remember him : same m.o . as harvey golden viper venom : His body is still warm , he must 've died within the last hour : Which means the killer was barely out the door when the acrobat found him : Do you think it 's the work of a hitman ?", [[44, 50, "PERSON"]]], ["else could link harvey and sake to the same killer ?", [[16, 22, "PERSON"], [27, 31, "PERSON"]]], ["m.o . as harvey . things", [[9, 15, "PERSON"]]], ["probably by the same assassin who tok harvey 's life . royales", [[38, 44, "PERSON"]]], ["harvey , less than month ago . And", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["'s mlrders do n't seem related to harvey 's or sake 's . the", [[34, 40, "PERSON"], [47, 51, "PERSON"]]], ["there 's sake , murdered by the same assassin as harvey soon after the night that weird lady supposedly saw lune at the carmine : december 26th , hmmm . only", [[49, 55, "PERSON"], [9, 13, "PERSON"]]], ["detective wood i 'm sorry again you have to do this because of me il see you tomorrow no", [[10, 14, "PERSON"], [10, 14, "PERSON"]]], ["am hecate , enchantress of the night . I", [[3, 9, "PERSON"]]], ["'re the elites . hephaestus", [[17, 27, "PERSON"]]], ["else hugues captnn , herminn imprecinct 0 8 !", [[5, 11, "PERSON"]]], ["had a lot on my mind too Drama queens slukr Captain hermann , this is for you , sir : Clackl", [[52, 59, "PERSON"]]], ["'ll be at the golden clover tomorrow night at iopm , per his routine : i 'll search his house before meeting you there . hermann", [[121, 128, "PERSON"], [14, 27, "LOC"]]], ["they 've been doing an incredible job infuriating hermann . oh", [[50, 57, "PERSON"]]], ["seem quite fond of that music box are n't y Lal we should really go back to the precinct they are probably waiting for our depositions and infuriating hermann is really not on my bucket list this morning Golden viper , you say ?", [[151, 158, "PERSON"]]], ["the way . hermann", [[10, 17, "PERSON"]]], [", he is n't completely wrong but to be honest , i think this is personal for hermann . The", [[77, 84, "PERSON"]]], ["only a couple weeks , lune 's unmasked more phantom scythe members than hermann ever has . and", [[72, 79, "PERSON"], [44, 51, "PERSON"], [52, 58, "PERSON"]]], ["would n't be surprised if \" catching lune \" is just hermann glnning for a promotion : vmp", [[52, 59, "PERSON"]]], ["nothing from hermann ?", [[13, 20, "PERSON"]]], ["only weapon i saw was a sword of all things : Remarkablei captain hermann is at second crime scene , waiting for you to report . but", [[66, 73, "PERSON"]]], ["ain hermann is here ?", [[4, 11, "PERSON"]]], ["captain hermann ilth precinct ardhalis police department Captain hermann !", [[8, 15, "PERSON"]]], ["hermann", [[0, 7, "PERSON"]]], ["'ve been thinking about the mission hermann gave 4s this morning . I", [[36, 43, "PERSON"]]], ["'d rather be on a romantic picnic with hermann than get lost with you again . of", [[39, 46, "PERSON"]]], ["have let her get lost in the city alone ah , also U a i can plan a romantic picnic between you and hermann anytime you want . Please", [[99, 106, "PERSON"]]], ["really want to find lune before hermann does . Cliu", [[32, 39, "PERSON"]]], ["matter the culprit this is what hermann chose 4s for Pa You can count on us , march . We", [[32, 39, "PERSON"], [78, 83, "PERSON"]]], ["hermann", [[0, 7, "PERSON"]]], ["'m sure hermann will gladly share : ah , by the way , my spying turned up a hunt for lune suspects in the precinct . detective", [[8, 15, "PERSON"]]], ["'m not surprised they suspect me : i have n't been at any of the phantom scythe arrests lately I 'm shocked hermann has n't already pinned it on me . he", [[108, 115, "PERSON"], [65, 72, "PERSON"], [73, 79, "PERSON"]]], ["all this , i almost forgot hermann needs to see me in his office !", [[27, 34, "PERSON"]]], ["; it 's you : I 'm fixing the paperwork for hermann : V", [[44, 51, "PERSON"]]], ["do n't want to get scolded by hermann again either . that", [[30, 37, "PERSON"]]], ["have something to give hermann , i gless . So", [[23, 30, "PERSON"]]], ["the ticket proceeds all g0 to charity huh ; hermann mentioned that a few weeks ago . the", [[44, 51, "PERSON"]]], ["have a meeting in the briefing room : you better go before i request you three as my next shooting practice targets after that , you 'd be silent forever Greetings , captain hermanni stfep Good morning to all as many of you already know , two high priority citizens were murdered last night , in the 11th precinct . We", [[174, 181, "PERSON"]]], ["Hermann", [[0, 7, "PERSON"]]], ["viper venom might be expensive , but it 's nothing your family ca n't afford Hermann , back down . We", [[77, 84, "PERSON"]]], ["officially , at least , except in hermann 's eyes . With", [[34, 41, "PERSON"]]], ["hermann . my", [[0, 7, "PERSON"]]], ["itmua [ w captain hermann , if i may interject . lalren", [[18, 25, "PERSON"]]], ["hermann gon na say about that I'l deal with him . i", [[0, 7, "PERSON"]]], ["it was n't for hermann pvil No , you do n't have to thank me . i", [[15, 22, "PERSON"]]], ["probably would 've been too scared to face hermann again : hahai hahaha , you 're welcome . Elows", [[43, 50, "PERSON"]]], ["Hermann", [[0, 7, "PERSON"]]], [", hermann 's singling yol out like he never has anyone else : I suppose i gave him a good reason to . Then", [[2, 9, "PERSON"]]], ["hermann", [[0, 7, "PERSON"]]], ["can call hermann over to revive you . Ahhhh", [[9, 16, "PERSON"]]], ["did hermann say ?", [[4, 11, "PERSON"]]], ["Hermann will not be able to keep you on suspension without more evidence . i", [[0, 7, "PERSON"]]], ["knowing hermann was reviewing the candidatures . [", [[8, 15, "PERSON"]]], ["Hahaha hahahahaha ahhahahahi h Nh Hermann speaking this is lieutenant hap hawkes . requesting", [[34, 41, "PERSON"], [74, 80, "PERSON"], [74, 80, "PERSON"], [74, 80, "PERSON"], [74, 80, "PERSON"]]], ["hermann wants 4s to go to the glass factory located on 73 sherbrooke street . more", [[0, 7, "PERSON"]]], ["jane 0nn f unna ta | aa Jne aan jne dorroel eroia aaaal rion | avml it was n't an accident ?", [[0, 4, "PERSON"]]], ["Lonely traveler ' s inn emplovee onlv Have you seen ms johnson today ?", [[55, 62, "PERSON"]]], ["johnson ; i 've brought a splint for your wrist stabilizing it will hopefully reduce the pain and the risk of injury . but", [[0, 7, "PERSON"]]], ["italian pizza cooper sqq which is typical of you : but seriously what were you up to ?", [[14, 20, "PERSON"]]], ["only want your cooperation answering a few qlestions What do you mean ?", [[15, 21, "PERSON"]]], ["torture really worked i would n't be here today we already know about your involvement in this operation , there 's no use denying it cooperate and perhaps we 'll let you and the people you care about live while longer . you", [[134, 140, "PERSON"]]], ["you want the kid to live , you 'd better cooperate and keep your mouth shut about what happened tonight . one", [[41, 47, "PERSON"]]], ["'ll cooperate , i swear !", [[4, 10, "PERSON"]]], ["cooperation has been much appreciated i strongly suggest you keep it up for the police if you want your trip to jail to be painless ckl bam ' pwbl ruble Hutt hdp Wft", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["hyacinth Episode 0 detective cooper , you will be in charge of this case . detective", [[29, 35, "PERSON"]]], ["thank you for your understanding and cooperation . How", [[37, 43, "PERSON"]]], ["you for your cooperaton !", [[13, 19, "PERSON"]]], ["ca n't believe i 'm here cooperating with him just like before . But", [[25, 31, "PERSON"]]], ["figured you might not be very cooperative at first , so i took precaltions . If", [[30, 36, "PERSON"]]], ["unit will cooperate with other precincts to look for the culprit . With", [[10, 16, "PERSON"]]], ["do they always repeat the same thing every year At least now that i 'm retired from my functions in the royal army i have more time for myself and my dear josephine . As", [[155, 164, "PERSON"]]], ["'re the only patrol unit on scene , i do n't know what it 's my job , lieutenant hawkes we 're here maintain peace , we should never answer with violence unless absolutely unavoidable but you said your unit was here !", [[81, 87, "PERSON"], [81, 87, "PERSON"], [81, 87, "PERSON"], [81, 87, "PERSON"]]], ["am afraid that lieutenant hawkes is right . Uncle", [[26, 32, "PERSON"], [26, 32, "PERSON"], [26, 32, "PERSON"], [26, 32, "PERSON"]]], ["hawkes speaking We are at the intersection of delph street and saint isidore street . skzke", [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["hawkes ?", [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["we must all live close to the crime scene lieutenant william hawkes patrol unit 1th precinct ardhalis police department i", [[61, 67, "PERSON"], [56, 60, "PERSON"], [61, 67, "PERSON"], [61, 67, "PERSON"], [53, 60, "PERSON"], [61, 67, "PERSON"]]], ["hawkes !", [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["on earth are you doing , hawkes ?", [[25, 31, "PERSON"], [25, 31, "PERSON"], [25, 31, "PERSON"], [25, 31, "PERSON"]]], ["hawkes ?", [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["i 'm lieutenant hawkes . We", [[16, 22, "PERSON"], [16, 22, "PERSON"], [16, 22, "PERSON"], [16, 22, "PERSON"]]], ["hawkes ?", [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["if i startled you : i 'm afraid i overheard your conversation : oh we 're so sorry mr hawkes !", [[86, 92, "PERSON"], [86, 92, "PERSON"], [86, 92, "PERSON"], [86, 92, "PERSON"]]], ["hawkes , i typed up the schedule you asked for !", [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["'s part was fine but because of yours it all looks sloppy hawkes unacceptable this does't send very good image of you to our higher ups bint / bhnf I 've never seen him get scolded like that never seen him make a mistake either . his", [[58, 64, "PERSON"], [58, 64, "PERSON"], [58, 64, "PERSON"], [58, 64, "PERSON"]]], ["also invited the hawkes , so expect young william too Feel free to bring your mysterious date as well . I", [[17, 23, "PERSON"], [45, 49, "PERSON"], [17, 23, "PERSON"], [17, 23, "PERSON"], [42, 49, "PERSON"], [17, 23, "PERSON"]]], ["it might be my last i just drowned sergeant hawkes paperwork in coffee again so", [[44, 50, "PERSON"], [44, 50, "PERSON"], [44, 50, "PERSON"], [44, 50, "PERSON"]]], ["yes yesi see you tomorrow ms . desroses bye lieutenant hawkes !", [[55, 61, "PERSON"], [31, 39, "PERSON"], [55, 61, "PERSON"], [55, 61, "PERSON"], [55, 61, "PERSON"]]], ["now that i 'm fully retired , it 's yolr duty to uphold the family name : The hawkes have always been held in high esteem by the royal family and the public . Yes", [[78, 84, "PERSON"], [78, 84, "PERSON"], [78, 84, "PERSON"], [78, 84, "PERSON"]]], ["saying goodbye : i 'm afraid all that weight of the hawkes family fell on william 's shoulders afterwards . Ap", [[52, 58, "PERSON"], [77, 81, "PERSON"], [52, 58, "PERSON"], [52, 58, "PERSON"], [74, 81, "PERSON"], [52, 58, "PERSON"]]], ["only says that because she does nt remember Stop encouraging her , randalli do n't listen to hawkes he 's not good for you : randalli", [[93, 99, "PERSON"], [67, 74, "PERSON"], [93, 99, "PERSON"], [93, 99, "PERSON"], [93, 99, "PERSON"]]], ["you so much , duke hawkes . it", [[19, 25, "PERSON"], [19, 25, "PERSON"], [19, 25, "PERSON"], [19, 25, "PERSON"]]], ["much as we love coming here each year we ca n't stay long , we must return to her side : totally understandable , hawkes . s", [[114, 120, "PERSON"], [114, 120, "PERSON"], [114, 120, "PERSON"], [114, 120, "PERSON"]]], ["can hear you , hawkes there 's nothing to worry about , will , really . maybe", [[15, 21, "PERSON"], [15, 21, "PERSON"], [15, 21, "PERSON"], [15, 21, "PERSON"]]], ["members Assassinated even when i became chief after hawkes ' promotion ; i barely had any information on this . it", [[52, 58, "PERSON"], [52, 58, "PERSON"], [52, 58, "PERSON"], [52, 58, "PERSON"]]], ["the highest ministers , the secret services and hawkes knew about this at the time . is", [[48, 54, "PERSON"], [48, 54, "PERSON"], [48, 54, "PERSON"], [48, 54, "PERSON"]]], [", all officers st ll and hawkes report to the precinct . This", [[25, 31, "PERSON"], [25, 31, "PERSON"], [25, 31, "PERSON"], [25, 31, "PERSON"]]], ["is lieutenant hawkes requesting transport . We", [[14, 20, "PERSON"], [14, 20, "PERSON"], [14, 20, "PERSON"], [14, 20, "PERSON"]]], ["lilk Hawkes please report to the precinct . This", [[5, 11, "PERSON"], [5, 11, "PERSON"], [5, 11, "PERSON"], [5, 11, "PERSON"]]], ["is lieutenant hawkes requesting transport . cllrk", [[14, 20, "PERSON"], [14, 20, "PERSON"], [14, 20, "PERSON"], [14, 20, "PERSON"]]], ["Lieutenant hawkes , i assume you were able to hear the message from lune . i", [[11, 17, "PERSON"], [11, 17, "PERSON"], [11, 17, "PERSON"], [11, 17, "PERSON"]]], ["'s office ms . karen", [[15, 20, "PERSON"]]], ["smith Good evening i 'm karen smith , the owner of this establishment to what do i owe this particular pleasure ?", [[24, 29, "PERSON"], [0, 5, "PERSON"]]], ["'re one of the last people who saw mr kevin chow alive . can", [[38, 43, "PERSON"], [44, 48, "PERSON"]]], ["really think could hurt kevin ?", [[24, 29, "PERSON"]]], ["long have you and chow known each other ?", [[18, 22, "PERSON"]]], ["you know if there was anyone who might want to hurt chow ?", [[52, 56, "PERSON"]]], [", do n't be so humble , sake : you absolutely do You said you used to work at chow 's mines . With", [[78, 82, "PERSON"], [24, 28, "PERSON"]]], ["Chow", [[0, 4, "PERSON"]]], ["do n't really know yet nothing for the time being but i have n't given up trying to free chow 's ex wife sid Lalren . could", [[89, 93, "PERSON"]]], ["I have what you need to prove sake 's guilt in chow 's case .", [[47, 51, "PERSON"], [30, 34, "PERSON"]]], ["could n't resist the temptation to look into chow 's case file . the", [[45, 49, "PERSON"]]], ["he snuck out of his apartment to murder chow . and", [[40, 44, "PERSON"]]], ["used t live right next t the alley where sake murdered chow . She", [[55, 59, "PERSON"], [41, 45, "PERSON"]]], ["did n't talk about chow 's case then . but", [[19, 23, "PERSON"]]], ["helped working on chow 's case : i did nt kill him !", [[18, 22, "PERSON"]]], ["wo n't do anything Ti ghten Actlally i 've meant to i 've meant to thank you for helping me with chow 's case . Grip", [[97, 101, "PERSON"]]], ["look at the disastrous outcome of chow 's case . Forgive", [[34, 38, "PERSON"]]], ["me , but if there 's one thing chow 's case teaches us is that there are calses that must be defended . even", [[31, 35, "PERSON"]]], ["sake 's mrder , and the new leads from chow 's case dri i wolldn't be surprised if she tried to investigate that circus further . but", [[39, 43, "PERSON"], [0, 4, "PERSON"]]], ["it 's done . Kieran", [[13, 19, "PERSON"]]], ["Kieran", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["know , it 's not very polite to eavesdrop Mister ph . or rather : Kieran Let 's make it spicy . co", [[66, 72, "PERSON"]]], ["You know , it 's not very polite to eavesdrop . Kieran", [[48, 54, "PERSON"]]], ["very perceptive of you , kieran : and the seventh does n't suspect you ?", [[25, 31, "PERSON"]]], ["'m still at kierans place . Purple", [[12, 18, "PERSON"]]], ["should n't be looking through his stuff grip Kieran ?", [[45, 51, "PERSON"]]], ["Kieran", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["did n't know we had to tell each other everything about our hobbies how can i trust you after this , kieran ?", [[101, 107, "PERSON"]]], ["he 's one of few remaining founders of the phantom scythe one the only people who could identify the leader kieran knew apostle vi !", [[108, 114, "PERSON"], [101, 107, "PERSON"], [43, 50, "PERSON"], [51, 57, "PERSON"]]], ["sent orders via messenger the only person who 's seen their face Kieran said the remaining members will be meeting with the messenger it 's only a few days from now . That", [[65, 71, "PERSON"], [16, 25, "PERSON"]]], ["au We 'll go over the questions you sent on instagram If kieran and lauren were about to fall off of a cliff and you could only save one from death , who would you save ?", [[57, 63, "PERSON"], [68, 74, "PERSON"]]], ["kieran", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["eph to do the research for me and then only send screenshots of what she judges acceptable for my eyes if not ; describe it to me sometimes even ask my assistants to draw them cuz i m just like \" no is kieran and lauren going to be a thing ?", [[202, 208, "PERSON"], [213, 219, "PERSON"]]], ["imcrying ) and i d be in the holding cell for suspicious activities due to posing for my own references : what if kieran got a short haircut ?", [[114, 120, "PERSON"]]], ["really liked to hug people like kym and was like grumpy cat : though , i'd alway subconsciously avoid her at the perfect timina and she alwavs end falling or hitting a desk or someth ( sorry not sorry eph ) that 's our tearierker bonding story if kieran was n't a mass urderer ; what would he be ?", [[247, 253, "PERSON"]]], ["22 kieran 24 kym 21 william 23 where are you from ?", [[3, 9, "PERSON"], [23, 27, "PERSON"], [20, 27, "PERSON"]]], ["name is kieran white he will be our new archivist and is nt he charminnnng ?", [[8, 14, "PERSON"], [15, 20, "PERSON"]]], ["has n't even been a day Do not test my patience , kieran . What", [[50, 56, "PERSON"]]], ["s Culck Dpip dpip Tump vmp Pvll Coltir sufrt Pvs7y ' wtl Racel : olfc 4 sindoir \" toh Als hey , kieran . Hm", [[96, 102, "PERSON"]]], ["one kieran said was involved in apostle vi !", [[4, 10, "PERSON"]]], ["Kk Wp grll Ziu Kieran ?", [[15, 21, "PERSON"]]], [": kieran there 's someone coming from the other side too t 7 they", [[2, 8, "PERSON"]]], ["thank you kieran !", [[10, 16, "PERSON"]]], ["take everything you 've got , kieran . I", [[30, 36, "PERSON"]]], ["ca n't even remember life before kieran . Maybe", [[33, 39, "PERSON"]]], ["it 's kieran delivering them to me il review the whole precinct archives . Oh", [[6, 12, "PERSON"]]], [", kieran what are you doing ?", [[2, 8, "PERSON"]]], ["you said kieran was n't your type oh", [[9, 15, "PERSON"]]], ["unlike you , kieran . she", [[13, 19, "PERSON"]]], ["off your high horse , kieran . I", [[22, 28, "PERSON"]]], ["sons eon Ja and he knows who kieran is ?", [[29, 35, "PERSON"]]], ["not become the monster they want you to be you hear me , kieran ?", [[57, 63, "PERSON"]]], ["un kieran was right . Great", [[3, 9, "PERSON"]]], [". Kieran", [[2, 8, "PERSON"]]], ["Kieran", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["kieran 's also inited ?", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["kieran , what were you doing before the apd ?", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["that true , kieran ?", [[12, 18, "PERSON"]]], ["really kieran is that true ?", [[7, 13, "PERSON"]]], ["sigl Hey kieran . 7", [[9, 15, "PERSON"]]], ["hyacinth Episode Hey kieran , where are you going ?", [[21, 27, "PERSON"]]], ["'re not really my coworkers and even less my friends Il see you around Wait , i pvll Look , kieran , you . you", [[92, 98, "PERSON"]]], ["you , kieran Shvt", [[6, 12, "PERSON"]]], ["last one standing winsi Losers have to g0 sing on stagei Kieran is joining !", [[57, 63, "PERSON"]]], ["es Yeet our first contest ant kieran white !", [[30, 36, "PERSON"], [37, 42, "PERSON"]]], ["Kieran . there", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["you hear , kieran ?", [[11, 17, "PERSON"]]], ["do n't think we should stay here . Kieran", [[35, 41, "PERSON"]]], ["trucks will be here in a couple of hours . Kieran", [[43, 49, "PERSON"]]], ["They even have a police issued radio transceiver to intercept communications from our personal radios Kieran , can you disguise your voice ?", [[102, 108, "PERSON"]]], ["whiteriver street ?", [[0, 5, "PERSON"]]], ["hyacinth Episode Whiteriver street whiteriver street Kym !", [[17, 22, "PERSON"]]], ["have mlltiple meanings , depending on the color like white ones mean sincerity do you know what the purple hyacinths mean ?", [[53, 58, "PERSON"]]], ["white . St", [[0, 5, "PERSON"]]], ["to meet you , mr white . I", [[17, 22, "PERSON"]]], ["'re you doing mr . white ?", [[19, 24, "PERSON"]]], ["really like you , mr white !", [[21, 26, "PERSON"]]], [". white is herei let 's go in !", [[2, 7, "PERSON"]]], ["mr . white . Sorry", [[5, 10, "PERSON"]]], ["randall thanks for the file , mr white . have", [[33, 38, "PERSON"], [0, 7, "PERSON"]]], [", this is special agent white swan . Agent", [[24, 29, "PERSON"]]], ["swan special white And", [[13, 18, "PERSON"]]], [", it was just koko !", [[14, 18, "PERSON"]]], ["many times have i told you not to ruin the zen garden pattern , koko ?", [[64, 68, "PERSON"]]], ["Krist", [[0, 5, "PERSON"]]], ["schaefferi you are under arrest for planting a bomb in the homstons theateri tell us how to defuse it and", [[0, 9, "PERSON"]]], ["lady arthinghami My beautiful handsome but", [[5, 15, "PERSON"]]], ["We know lune is two people : based on what miss arthingham said , one is still likely a man . the", [[48, 58, "PERSON"]]], ["'s maid alerted the police . they", [[3, 7, "PERSON"]]], ["lucky He probably did n't consider that the maid would be awake or that the police could respond as soon as we did . it", [[44, 48, "PERSON"]]], ["one time chance to switch career paths Fortun teller gelat Ahnl Maiden of the moon . I", [[64, 68, "PERSON"]]], ["leaving here : Okay Do n't worry about the glass , i'l ask maid to take care of it . alright", [[59, 63, "PERSON"]]], ["wo nt make it in timei lauren do nt !", [[23, 29, "PERSON"]]], ["Unclei that mani we ca n't let him go , we must interrogate him lauren !", [[64, 70, "PERSON"]]], ["'s Lauren , i know you must be right but now is not the time and you know better than anyone that to open an investigation we must have solid proof your hunches ca n't overrule the law . Remember", [[3, 9, "PERSON"]]], ["'m very sorry lauren : i do believe in you . L", [[14, 20, "PERSON"]]], ["excuse me , i have meeting to attend see you tonight , lauren !", [[55, 61, "PERSON"]]], ["'s been a pleasure , lauren . Sung", [[21, 27, "PERSON"]]], ["Ardhalis police department vi Lauren ?", [[30, 36, "PERSON"]]], ["swear i 'm going to accidentally stab you if you keep doing this sla \" My dear lauren , your pretty golden eyes look pensive tod stop !", [[79, 85, "PERSON"]]], ["aye lauren !", [[4, 10, "PERSON"]]], ["Lauren ?", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["laurenww !", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["eveving , lady lauren !", [[15, 21, "PERSON"]]], ["have been told so often to turn the page that it 's become almost shameful for me to admit Lauren . it", [[91, 97, "PERSON"]]], ["'s up to you to find the strength to let go The boy is dead lauren If", [[60, 66, "PERSON"]]], [", lauren . well", [[2, 8, "PERSON"]]], ["happened in the golden clover that night wo n't happen again : Lauren ?", [[63, 69, "PERSON"], [16, 29, "LOC"]]], ["lauren : Yeah", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["march , please protect the witnessi lauren kym with mei @ang |", [[36, 42, "PERSON"], [0, 5, "PERSON"]]], ["Over therei Someone escaped through the windowsi Lauren wait !", [[49, 55, "PERSON"]]], ["Laureni", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], [", lauren !", [[2, 8, "PERSON"]]], ["Seriously , you must be the most stubborn person i 've ever met . Laureni", [[66, 72, "PERSON"]]], ["see that you 've slept well Obviously more than you did Lauren : your face . hlh", [[56, 62, "PERSON"]]], ["trusted him all this timei Are n't you coming with us , lauren ?", [[56, 62, "PERSON"]]], ["why would the king Lauren : sigh s He", [[19, 25, "PERSON"]]], ["ah dozens of prison guards and all lunes convicts slaughtered purple hyacinth has struck again than W fo ' % mol : 88 ama/ Lauren , are you okay ?", [[123, 129, "PERSON"]]], ["every person they expose going to meet the same fate Stop Clent Lauren , you 're not coming ?", [[64, 70, "PERSON"]]], ["please , lauren . vish", [[9, 15, "PERSON"]]], ["condemn me for my crimes , but who 's worse between us , lauren ?", [[57, 63, "PERSON"]]], ["Really lauren how foolish of you . He", [[7, 13, "PERSON"]]], ["all due respect captain , should n't this mission go to lauren ?", [[56, 62, "PERSON"]]], ["wonder he hates lauren . I", [[16, 22, "PERSON"]]], ["tq laureni Are you okay ?", [[3, 9, "PERSON"]]], ["'s go lauren you should get some rest first i", [[6, 12, "PERSON"]]], ["lauren !", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["'m fine , lauren . stay", [[10, 16, "PERSON"]]], ["Oh , lauren !", [[5, 11, "PERSON"]]], ["Lauren how do you pronounce ' hyacinth \" ?", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["lauren", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["wink Are nt we lauren ?", [[15, 21, "PERSON"]]], ["what happened this morning lauren ?", [[27, 33, "PERSON"]]], ["lauren , everything seems fine or now , but you should rest for the next two days least try to avoid activities that reqlire high concentration they calse any symptoms worsen : same thing for physical activities write for hoh shicts this week and strongly recommend you take frequent breaks your headache comes back , you may take twc of pills every tfosr six holrs thank you very much for watching over me oday il try behave you better , yolng lady would love not have see you again . you", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["m channeling laureni you", [[13, 19, "PERSON"]]], ["lauren . goddess", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["turn on your sound Purple hyacinth Episode Do n't be stupid , lauren you have better things to do than panic . With", [[62, 68, "PERSON"]]], ["hyacinth Episode No lauren . no", [[20, 26, "PERSON"]]], ["the way , have you seen lauren ?", [[24, 30, "PERSON"]]], [", lauren , you did n't even tell your friends ?", [[2, 8, "PERSON"]]], ["ca nt tell themi Lauren and i are dating hh", [[17, 23, "PERSON"]]], ["hyacinth Episode Lauren and i are dating I ih Hw", [[17, 23, "PERSON"]]], ["could you hide this from us lauren ?", [[28, 34, "PERSON"]]], ["lauren ?", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["m so proud of you , lauren my girl is finally getting somei !", [[20, 26, "PERSON"]]], ["morning , laureni you 're just getting home ?", [[10, 16, "PERSON"]]], ["basically admitted his involvement in allendale . laureni", [[50, 56, "PERSON"], [38, 48, "LOC"]]], ["shame in losing him lauren no one 's even got near him in the seven years he 's been active You 're lucky to be alive . Purple", [[20, 26, "PERSON"]]], ["to see he still has it out for you ) lauren . are", [[37, 43, "PERSON"]]], ["Lauren", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["you tomorrow lauren !", [[13, 19, "PERSON"]]], ["may think your enemies are hidden in the shadows but he is closer t you ; more similar to you than you think , lalren you must remove the blindfoldi open your eyes , lauren !", [[166, 172, "PERSON"]]], ["youk ey5 ) , lauren ?", [[13, 19, "PERSON"]]], ["he is closer to you more similar to you than you think , lauren . Anml", [[57, 63, "PERSON"]]], [": Lauren and i slept as much as you did and we 're perfectly fine . wrong", [[2, 8, "PERSON"]]], ["lauren never sleeps . guilty !", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["Lauren", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["' murder le Oh , lauren . i", [[17, 23, "PERSON"]]], ["is going to be a very long day Hlsi Cuk whltk Laureni Hey , guys . Have", [[46, 52, "PERSON"]]], ["could 've drugged her with the black market sedative lauren found on him last year . and", [[53, 59, "PERSON"]]], ["that Someone around you has or will stab you in the back does n't sound like anything good open your eyes , laureni If", [[108, 114, "PERSON"]]], [", laureni pos 06 caela cgodn Why", [[2, 8, "PERSON"]]], [": Get down laureni you", [[11, 17, "PERSON"]]], ["Laureni", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["'s been over a year and they still think i 'm unfit for duty Purple hyacinth Episode 8 aye , lauren !", [[93, 99, "PERSON"]]], ["n't even know what that word means see ya lauren !", [[42, 48, "PERSON"]]], ["Your pretty golden eyes look pensive today , dear lauren . i", [[50, 56, "PERSON"]]], ["swear i 'll hit the next person who says pensive \" ' eyes \" and \" lauren \" in the same sentence There is no escape !", [[66, 72, "PERSON"]]], ["Okay will , but who really makes you feel like lauren . I", [[47, 53, "PERSON"]]], ["'s good for her , i suppose : So hapy tmul yolre not murderer laureni !", [[62, 68, "PERSON"]]], ["would you like to order anything , ma'am 0 ' lauren goddess of deduction . Lend", [[45, 51, "PERSON"]]], ["lauren", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["'ve been chasing the leader one man for a decade and they do nt have even a single clue who he isi How can we trust them ?", [[21, 27, "PERSON"]]], ["might be my only chance of finding the leader : eef . tick", [[39, 45, "PERSON"]]], ["'re the leader 's favorite puppet , you obey his every word aw , please , that 's insulting !", [[8, 14, "PERSON"]]], ["leader might not be venerated by everyone , but he 's certainly feared by all his pawns are everywhere no one knows who he is but killing for him , doing his dirty work and being the best at it . that", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["least , that 's the \" official version \" considering the leader 's a mystery no one knows his real goal . justice", [[57, 63, "PERSON"]]], ["What do you know about the leader ?", [[27, 33, "PERSON"]]], ["i 'm honestly surprised leader has n't asked me to finish him yet", [[24, 30, "PERSON"]]], ["ten years ago , the leader promised us a better world , free from the tyranny of the royals !", [[20, 26, "PERSON"]]], ["from the leader : Purple hyacinth Episode 1 7 hours ago : .. Sh", [[9, 15, "PERSON"]]], ["do n't know who the seventh apostle is i do n't think anybody does except the leader !", [[78, 84, "PERSON"]]], ["leader seems quite bold for ordering such a thing . i", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["For a decade , they terrorized ardhalis city a6:0 No one had ever seen their leader terrorists Thieves Killers All united We called them : . The", [[77, 83, "PERSON"]]], ["'s unheard they all believed it was the leader 's plan and not the apostle taking over the reins himself the apostle as you can guess the apostle is furious an !", [[40, 46, "PERSON"]]], ["'s just say your little \" secret \" operation is doing so poorly that it 's only a matter of time before the leader wants all of you dead . after", [[108, 114, "PERSON"]]], ["i find hilarious is that the bunch of you believed your operation could pass under the leader 's radar : I do n't think that anyone expected such a fiasco but only the pawns have been eliminated from the chessboard so far the master pieces are still well in place are n't you afraid the leader will exterminate you all ?", [[87, 93, "PERSON"]]], ["i 'm sure the leader will eventually want to get rid of all of Them So the leader charged you to keep an eye on the operation for him and take care of the nuisances at the same time . Haha", [[14, 20, "PERSON"]]], ["spy the leader planted in the m1th precinct . he", [[8, 14, "PERSON"]]], ["colleague was getting useless , so the leader wanted him removed . I", [[39, 45, "PERSON"]]], ["know nothing about him , but if he came from a poorer background the leader 's mission could 've sounded appealing to him . Or", [[69, 75, "PERSON"]]], ["where s your leader ?", [[13, 19, "PERSON"]]], ["bravery of the ignorant i suppose : look , i do n't know who you think you are , But i made a promise to find your leader and make sure he faces justice . Whatever", [[115, 121, "PERSON"]]], ["'m sure n voud ffu om Police officers despise the leader , but not nearly as much as you do . your", [[50, 56, "PERSON"]]], ["i share the same goal to find the leader and destroy him : What ?", [[34, 40, "PERSON"]]], ["i can see he 's not lying so even the assassins do nt who their leader is ?", [[64, 70, "PERSON"]]], ["'re a police officer and i 'm an assassin if we pool our resources , we might actually have a shot at finding the leader . we", [[114, 120, "PERSON"]]], ["m going to help you find the leader and in exchange , you 're going to drop that gun and let me walk free : If you 're fool enough to try to throw me in jail , you wo n't get anything out of me besides , either way i 'm going to escape you 're cuffed with a gln pointed at your head aw", [[29, 35, "PERSON"]]], ["the leader send you to free me ?", [[4, 10, "PERSON"]]], ["will prevent him from infiltrating the castle next time the leader did n't send his most infamous assassin there for nothing it was a calculated risk He is sending us a message : He had them killed before they could reveal anything more to the police . his", [[60, 66, "PERSON"]]], ["leader may order you to strike but there 's not a shred of remorse in you ps/", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["Whatever the leader told me to do , i did it . Ca", [[13, 19, "PERSON"]]], ["you also knew i could n't ignore the leader 's orders . If", [[37, 43, "PERSON"]]], ["leader is pleased with your work from yesterday . those", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["other assassin has ever made it up to the 15th floor and back alive : once again , you 've proven your resourcefulness and reliability the leader already has a new mission for you , purple hyacinth . Already", [[139, 145, "PERSON"]]], ["The leader wants you to find the traitors hiding under the name of lune and kill them The leader expects results shortly purple hyacinth . shiri", [[4, 10, "PERSON"]]], ["is the leader ?", [[7, 13, "PERSON"]]], ["with robrenad cap whal Weapon operation led by apostle viy the leader ' s orders objective : weapons", [[63, 69, "PERSON"]]], ["th vps who are the phantom june anonymou8 apoatlea terrorists , hlea tbievee , guppogedly killer8 fighting ' better an announcing themselves thej = viom hierarchy lilendale \" stazion = traqedy hietarc hy woung considenne the mystoy reporte d kows surrouc mixtidg eoa leader ; bellet bad > jusuce ; jured recently ievenge . kepl", [[267, 273, "PERSON"], [19, 26, "PERSON"]]], ["what is the leader planning ?", [[12, 18, "PERSON"]]], ["the leader sent you here to kill them all like you did at the tower ?", [[4, 10, "PERSON"]]], ["leader did n't put me here simply to be a replacement spy What do you mean ?", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["if him breathing down my neck at the precinct is n't enough : now the leader is Officially after us . i", [[70, 76, "PERSON"]]], ["'m supposed to find and kill lune : usually when i receive such missions , the leader expects evidence . And", [[79, 85, "PERSON"]]], ["'s probably here to report a new kill i bet he s all bark and no bitei he s the leaders favorite little pet his personal att ack dog !", [[80, 86, "PERSON"]]], ["brought the documents the leader wanted me to retrieve . as", [[26, 32, "PERSON"]]], ["leader will be pleased to hear about this . Also", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["we 'll be in contact soon : Well , thank you for the kind warning , comrade : But honestly who would be reckless enough to threaten the leader , huh ?", [[136, 142, "PERSON"]]], ["this brings the police or the leader down on all our heads , None of you will be keeping yours . The", [[30, 36, "PERSON"]]], ["leader has already gotten purple hyacinth involved who knows what else he suspfcts The weapons import was the leader 's plan first . You", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["leader might be silent , but he 's not stupid it would n't be surprising if he finds out sooner than later and then we 'll be as good as dead . what", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["the leader knows or not is irrelevant so long as he can not stop us netl saen scsbly oblla conp bw / hr Lud dd e this secret operation was a high risk for all of us , especially seven . and", [[4, 10, "PERSON"]]], ["he wo n't act until he has gathered all the necessary assets to overthrow the royals and the leader . Sadl", [[93, 99, "PERSON"]]], ["anw Delaying things only gives the police and the leader more time to figure it out !", [[50, 56, "PERSON"]]], ["now he 's giving us the same excuses there is a big difference betweeen the seven and the leader . our", [[90, 96, "PERSON"]]], ["just wants to take the power and free 4s all from the leader 's empty speeches and brutal grip . Clit", [[54, 60, "PERSON"]]], ["can tell the leader not to worry , messenger . You", [[13, 19, "PERSON"], [35, 44, "PERSON"]]], ["way to get to the leader . and", [[18, 24, "PERSON"]]], ["leader wants you to find the traitors hiding under the name of lune and kill them . I", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["the leader and destroy him . I", [[4, 10, "PERSON"]]], ["Killing people for the leader is much more lucrative . and", [[23, 29, "PERSON"]]], ["bad i arrived just in time to see him choke on his blood was that an order from the leader ?", [[84, 90, "PERSON"]]], ["leader will probably ask me to finish the job at some point but you seem very eager to keep her alive : how useful can she be ?", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["what you want Only you know what happens to people who disturb the leader 's plans . Aw", [[67, 73, "PERSON"]]], [", you 've been actively trying to unmask the leader and apostle vi !", [[45, 51, "PERSON"]]], ["leader himself . why", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], [", the leader was one of the snapdragon survivors . And", [[6, 12, "PERSON"]]], ["they survived the massacre even in its earliest days , the people to know the leader 's identity were extremely rare . And", [[78, 84, "PERSON"]]], ["already knew the leader was after them : They knew who he is . And", [[17, 23, "PERSON"]]], ["is nt lying He is nt lying he killed my parents becalse the leader ordered him to . Because", [[60, 66, "PERSON"]]], ["some point , the leader 's goal may have been justified but i 'm afraid what comes next is worse than anything we 've seen before . So", [[17, 23, "PERSON"]]], ["leader did n't say . maybe", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["leaders closest allies how how ?", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["is why the leader has always been so unforgiving of the people who want to abandon the ps . do", [[11, 17, "PERSON"]]], ["the secret services know anything about the leader 's next move ?", [[44, 50, "PERSON"]]], [", the leader was one of the snapdragon survivors . do", [[6, 12, "PERSON"]]], ["pushed the man before the leader over the edge : Is that why my parents followed him ?", [[26, 32, "PERSON"]]], ["leader wants you to keep an eye on the purple hyacinth . Keep", [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]], ["Th8p Th0p Did the leader finally decide to get rid of me ?", [[18, 24, "PERSON"]]], [", not going to lie , the leader is starting to lose his patience with lune . Who", [[25, 31, "PERSON"]]], ["my parents and the leader must have escaped cilklf The authorities probably did n't have their names . Since", [[19, 25, "PERSON"]]], ["they were n't as supportive of the leader 's ideas as you think . But", [[35, 41, "PERSON"]]], ["that , only the leader himself could tell Hey whatever your parents did , it changes nothing about who you are now and what you are fighting for . you", [[16, 22, "PERSON"]]], ["think you can stop the phantom scythe ?", [[23, 30, "PERSON"], [31, 37, "PERSON"]]], ["phantom scythe has dominated our city for the past decadei It", [[0, 7, "PERSON"], [8, 14, "PERSON"]]], ["shamei for all we know , some of them might be working for the phantom scythei Are nt you tired of being afraid to leave your homes ?", [[63, 70, "PERSON"], [71, 77, "PERSON"]]], [", fellow citizens , if we truly want to rid ourselves of the phantom scythe , we must unite our forces and not give way to such discord between us !", [[61, 68, "PERSON"], [69, 75, "PERSON"]]], ["mani He 's a phantom scythe memberi U siri Thank you so much , sir !", [[13, 20, "PERSON"], [21, 27, "PERSON"]]], ["draw attention from something else : l like involvement with the phantom scythe ?", [[65, 72, "PERSON"], [73, 79, "PERSON"]]], ["knew there were two flagrant criminals in this crowd but i could n't do anything about it they 're right the police are powerless the phantom scythe 's members walk the city freely knowing we 're too scared to arrest them no matter how fiercely we fight they 're always one step ahead . We", [[134, 141, "PERSON"], [142, 148, "PERSON"]]], ["'s exactly what the phantom scythe is spending its time and resources you know : making sure that the apd never gets past those dead ends look , i came here tonight because : i know you 've been honest with me i", [[20, 27, "PERSON"], [28, 34, "PERSON"]]], ["know ; officer it 's not all rainbows and unicorns in the phantom scythe it", [[58, 65, "PERSON"], [66, 72, "PERSON"]]], ["do n't want to be mixed up in any of your shady and illegal phantom scythe business . investigation", [[60, 67, "PERSON"], [68, 74, "PERSON"]]], ["you should also remember i was n't actually trying to kill you : So officer , what do you know about the phantom scythe ?", [[105, 112, "PERSON"], [113, 119, "PERSON"]]], ["four of which are the surviving originals the rest of the first round were either assassinated or killed themselves and i gless not all of them required replacements pelease How many